(Gen Z)
(Episode 12)
Take everything in moderation.
This is my reward for you.
-Here.
-Alright.
If so,
I'll take the entire pot.
I don't want to share it with you.
Just pour a little for me.
-Come on.
-Take everything in moderation.
You said so yourself.
-Just a little more.
-Stop drinking.
-Stop drinking. Have some food.
Alright.
Your mouth is so oily.
Wipe your mouth.
Stop drinking.
Wait. What are you doing?
Hey.
There's not much left.
-Just a little.
-Just a little?
-Yeah.
-Just a little, okay?
Only a little.
That's enough.
That's too much.
Cheers.
You don't understand, right?
Cheers is what they say in English.
Cheers.
How much did you drink?
How did you get so drunk?
I'll make some hangover soup for you.
Here.
Drink this.
Don't you know how much liquor
you can drink?
I'm teaching students in accordance
with their aptitude.
First, I lure her in with desire.
After that, I'll bring her to
the righteous path.
Tou Tou is a promising child.
It's just that it's difficult
to be her teacher.
Look at me.
I'm giving everything I got
to realise Master's dream.
I've never seen you put this much effort
in teaching Tian Zhen.
It's because I know
Tian Zhen
belongs here.
He can't run away.
But Tou Tou?
She might run away
if we take our eyes off her.
I think
you're sure that I won't run away.
That's why you make
endless demands of me.
Dear, that sounds unfair to me.
Unfair?
Was I wrong?
You put so much effort
in treating outsiders.
What about your family?
This is
a common problem among humans.
We always show outsiders
our best side
and show our family members
our worst side.
Don't think
that I invited Tou Tou to drink with me
so that I could transform her.
I was cleaning up the mess
your son had made.
If so, why didn't you let him
treat the girl during the forum?
So, you were waiting
to say that all along?
I was wondering
why everything
wasn't proceeding smoothly lately.
Your son wasn't ready yet.
If you don't let him give it a try,
he'll never be ready.
Both you
and Uncle were around.
And, he wanted to send Tian Zhen
to give the girl a diagnosis.
He wanted to see how capable
Tian Zhen was.
You only look on the bright side.
What if your son
made things worse?
If Tou Tou made things worse,
everyone could at least
come to terms with it.
I could back her up.
But if I send your son there
and back him up,
the Song family
will be embarrassed.
I didn't send your son there
in order to protect him.
Goodness.
This concerns the girl's life, you know?
Listen.
I'll tell you this.
Although Tou Tou is boorish,
she's talented.
She's talented
and she's meant to take this path.
She might be distracted
during our lessons,
however, she has a delicate heart.
Her eyes and ears were open
and receptive.
She remembered everything
I said and taught.
Not only did she observe what I taught,
but she could also apply them.
She observed that Mr Zheng's daughter
had eczema.
When your son was there,
he only said
that she had a fever.
He may be able to cure her fever,
but he'll never think of
making egg yolk oil on the scene
and letting the girl apply it.
Do you think he'll think of that?
He'll never think of that.
The people there might have
a doctorate or a Master's degree,
but none of them
can do any better than Tou Tou.
You're excited and proud
when you talk about Sun Tou Tou.
You feel like throwing up again?
I'll go to the toilet.
Li Quan applied for leave again?
Yes, this is already the second time
this month.
And, he applied for leave once
during our weekend lesson.
Tian Zhen,
did you know that Li Quan
applied for leave?
I know that.
Where did he go?
He...
He's doing a part-time job.
A part-time job?
What does that mean?
He's doing foot massages.
Dr Song,
someone left their belongings
in the storeroom.
Come and take a look.
Call Zhao Li Quan.
Tell him to pack his belongings.
How could he keep them here?
This is a medical centre, not a hotel.
The medicine we use
will be consumed by the patients.
Where will he stay then?
Take his things out.
How is that my business?
Tian Zhen,
is Li Quan facing any difficulties?
I lent him my dorm last time.
But the dorm had tight security.
I told him to stay here
for the time being.
I think he's going to rent a unit soon.
That's why he applied for leave
in order to work outside.
He should find a job
with stable income.
He can come and learn
when he has time.
If so, you can just give him a job.
Just make him a pharmaceutical worker.
He can prepare prescriptions.
He can study at the same time.
And, he'll make some money too.
Isn't that the best of both worlds?
Zhao Li Quan will be
a doctor in the future.
He can't just steal other people's jobs.
Go and ask him.
It's either he continues his study
or works outside.
You're discriminating against him here.
Why can Peng Shi Yan work
while studying then?
Why can't Zhao Li Quan do the same?
Peng Shi Yan
doesn't make a living
as a TCM practitioner.
TCM is Zhao Li Quan's livelihood.
He needs medical skills
to make a living, understood?
I think Tian Zhen's suggestion
is worth considering.
It might work.
If Li Quan is around,
at least he can help us out
when we're busy preparing prescriptions.
He's familiar with herbs and medicine.
And, he was professionally trained
in this field.
He can prepare prescriptions
when we give diagnoses.
He can study with the other classmates
when there's a class.
This is our place after all.
We can pay him according to
a part-timer's rate.
What do you think?
Niece-in-law already said so much.
Nephew,
why don't you consider it?
Why are you calling me Nephew again?
Because it's time for me
to show my authority as your senior.
I know you guys are
doing this for his sake.
But the thing is,
Zhao Li Quan
must understand what he truly desires.
That's the main thing.
That's it for now.
Call him.
He can't stay here.
So, does that mean
your father has agreed to it?
Your seniority does work wonders.
You've been applying for leave
just to work here?
Quit the job.
You're a postgraduate student
from a decent medical academy.
Why are you working
in a massage parlour?
I'll get you a decent job.
-Come with me.
-Tian Zhen.
Thank you.
You always helped me out.
I feel pretty bad about it.
I appreciate your kindness,
but I'm doing great here.
Doing great?
You apply for leave during the day.
You don't even attend
our lessons on the weekend.
My father was unhappy that
you applied for leave today.
Besides, if you work at night,
you won't have the energy to
attend class on the second day.
If there's a situation in your family,
-you can tell me.
-Tian Zhen.
I can help you out.
I know you're doing it for my sake.
But it's not like I can accept your help
every time without any pressure.
I'm a man too. I have my dignity.
You said this yourself.
You said you would find a mentor
in the apprentice class
and ask them to take you
under their wing.
How could you learn from them
when you're doing this?
I do want to get a mentor
and learn under them.
However, I need to survive first.
You saw this yourself.
I've always been working outside.
It was different when I was in college.
Back then, I was just
providing for myself.
I didn't need to provide for my family.
Now, it's different.
Now, I have to make money
and provide for my family.
Forget it. Let's drop the topic.
You won't understand anyway.
Your starting point is the endpoint
I've been trying to achieve.
Wait. What did you say?
-Wait.
-This is...
What are you guys saying?
You guys are going off-topic here.
It's way off-topic.
Is it that complicated?
Do you wish to find
a way for you to study
and make money at the same time?
Right now, there's such a deal.
It can satisfy your need to study
and help you make money too.
Do you want it or not?
Why are you here?
Why the heck are you here?
Didn't you come here
to help your friend?
You already arranged
something for him, right?
Just tell him.
Tell him everything.
Tell him both the pros and cons.
Let him make the call.
He's the one making the call here,
not you.
Why are you acting like
you're his father?
But you!
You kept interrupting him
when he was trying
to tell you about it.
I was so fed up.
Can't you just wait for him
to finish his words
before you interrupt?
Just cut to the chase.
Don't talk about anything else.
You can work as a pharmaceutical worker
in my family's medical centre.
You can attend class when there's one.
My father has already agreed to it.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Yeah.
Here you go.
Isn't it simple?
You guys would've argued
for three hours if I weren't here.
Quan,
you might not be able to
live in the medical centre anymore.
That's fine.
I'll get my wage soon.
I'll stay in a cheap place
for the time being.
Okay.
Fools.
Xing Xing.
We meet again.
Dear,
you're here to pick me up?
Someone's following me.
Is he gone?
He should be gone.
That was terrifying.
That guy followed me
all the way here from the subway.
He kept staring at me.
Listen. Next time, if you encounter
someone like him,
just stare at him.
People like him are timid.
I'm not Tou Tou.
I dare not stare at him.
What are you doing here?
I...
You must make sure
your centre of gravity
is between your legs.
Wait.
Who's calling you?
It's Xing Xing.
Hello?
Sun Tou Tou, what have you done?
What do you mean
by sending a guy to my house?
Xing Xing,
it's pretty late now.
Have you taken dinner?
Did you work overtime again?
I'm sure it's tough on you.
I'm heartbroken.
Don't interrupt me.
Tell me.
You sent a man to my house.
What should I do?
(Xing Xing, listen.)
Quan is so pitiful.
Not only can he not afford food,
but he also
can't afford a place to stay.
(My bed is vacant anyway.)
(That's why I sent him there.)
(Can you take pity on him)
and take him in?
I promise.
He's a good guy.
He won't cross the line.
I don't know if he's a good guy or not,
but he's a guy.
(That's even better.)
I thought it was dangerous for you
to live alone.
Now, there's a guy to protect you.
I can rest at ease now.
(And, Xing Xing, think about it.)
(He knows how to give massages.)
If you have issues like a stiff neck,
you don't even need to
go to the massage parlour.
Just stay at home.
First come, first served, right?
(Isn't it convenient?)
You'll land me in trouble eventually.
What? You expect me
to carry your luggage?
Slowly.
You must be careful when you go up.
-Come on.
-Let's continue.
Maintain your centre of gravity.
Okay.
Feel the harmony between man and nature.
Say,
is chiropractic
the thing
where they pop the bones?
That's not it.
Ms Dong doesn't do that.
It's dangerous when
you crack bones like that.
No, that's not what I mean.
I mean popping the bones.
There's a sound to it.
What's the difference between them?
Cracking
makes a different sound.
Popping makes a different sound.
That's the difference.
It's the same thing.
How could they be the same?
The difference is
that chiropractic is fake.
It's a lie.
It's already good enough
for massages and the likes
to help our bodies to relax.
We mustn't abuse
the power of rumours.
It'll harm the people.
That's why I think
TCM practitioners
can focus on healthcare
while doctors can focus on treatments.
We should stay on our designated trails.
Isn't that better?
I don't know about the others,
but Ms Dong is a living deity.
If she does work her magic,
you'll feel like you've been reborn.
I know her for many years.
I saw for myself
that patients in wheelchairs
could walk out of the room
after her treatment.
Guys, listen to him.
She used her hand
to restore the position of the bones,
and that could achieve
the effect of surgeries.
Don't you think it's ridiculous?
Even doctors can't guarantee
that a cripple could walk out of
the room after surgery.
Pick it up.
Look. He's resorting to this
when he can't win the argument.
You deserved it.
Shi Yan, you'd better believe it.
There's an old lady called Luo You Ming
in Shuangqiao, Beijing.
She could set bones
with just her hands.
Premier Zhou even
built a hospital for her.
She could
set fractures, even crushed bones
and restore them.
Is that Ms Dong
as good as the old lady
in Shuangqiao, Beijing?
If that's the case, she's even better
than my nephew then.
Yeah.
Is Mr Ren here?
This must be the classroom.
That's Zhu's car.
He's here?
Mr Ren!
I finally found you!
Mr Zhu,
I thought we had an appointment
in the medical centre on Monday?
I couldn't sleep well
for the past few days.
(Zhu Chang Ming)
I was flustered.
I couldn't wait any longer.
Mr Ren, please read my pulse.
(Dong Hui Ci)
Check my pulse.
Yeah.
I just received a batch of
top-quality cordyceps.
There are only 1,000 of them in one jin.
I bought 500,000 yuan
worth of cordyceps.
Should I consume it?
Or should I
consume the 60-years-old
wild ginseng I have?
What do you think?
What about this?
You can tell us
the "tonics"
you think that are good for you
lately.
I took plenty of them.
Turtles,
ginseng,
dendrobium, sea cucumbers,
I took everything.
So, do you feel better
after taking them?
Or do you feel uncomfortable?
It's like this.
I think it's only worth it
if I take such expensive tonics.
I make a lot of money.
What else should I spend them on
besides food?
So, you have too much money, huh?
You should do charity with them then.
You can donate to our apprentice class.
Mr Ren, it's like this.
I can't donate my money when I'm alive.
I'll donate everything to you
once I'm dead.
Donating my money
is just like donating my organs.
I'll feel terrible.
Zhu, you need to understand this.
Herbs and tonics are used
to rectify a deviation.
Not all tonics can be consumed.
Judging from your current condition,
it's useless
to take any kind of tonics.
Even so, I have to take something.
Give me a prescription.
You?
Listen.
Carrot and Chinese cabbages
are your best bet.
Seasonal and cheap ingredients
are best for you.
Just adjust your diet.
Take your meal on time
and sleep on time.
I can't sleep.
I wouldn't need to be here
if I could sleep in the first place.
What do you think?
Did you owe people money lately?
No.
Did someone owe you money?
Are you afraid that
you can't get it back?
I can't treat that.
Don't say that.
Mr Ren, you have to
do something about me.
You have to think of something.
You can't just ignore me.
What should I do then?
Give me a prescription.
Have you done some movements
that rotate your spine?
What do you mean?
He plays golf.
Did you play golf for the past few days?
I play golf twice per week.
I stopped playing golf after last week
as I couldn't sleep.
I didn't play golf this week.
Do you know something?
When you play golf,
you're rotating your spine
with this movement.
This movement
caused your thoracic vertebra
to shift to the wrong position.
And that has affected the function
of your lungs and heart.
That's why you couldn't sleep.
I'll restore them
to their original positions later.
You'll be able to sleep well tonight
after that.
You should give me a prescription.
If Ms Dong said she could treat you,
she could definitely treat you.
Are you sure?
Guys,
for our chiropractic class,
I've invited Ms Dong Hui Ci,
whom I respect a lot.
She bumped into
a patient at the entrance.
She's treating him right now.
That's why
I'm doing the introduction.
Ms Dong is here. Let's welcome her.
Ms Dong,
how's the patient?
He's asleep.
Professor Song is looking after him.
Guys,
for today's class,
it'll definitely be interesting and fun.
We'll show you guys
that not only can chiropractic
treat illness,
but it can also treat major illnesses.
Just now, that patient said
he had insomnia.
After Ms Dong's treatment,
he's already
fallen asleep.
Okay.
I'll leave this class
to Ms Dong.
Ms Dong, I'll go and check on him.
Please go ahead.
Okay.
I always think that TCM practitioners
are mystifying things.
Say, was that Mr Zhu acting just now?
I assume you think
that I requested Professor Ren
to stage an act
to show off the skills of my sect.
That's not it. Actually,
with our skills,
we can cure many illnesses.
Ms Dong, not only
do you know chiropractic,
but you can also read lips.
Hello, everyone.
In our daily lives,
we'll often encounter situations
such as
moving a flower pot,
carrying a baby,
wearing your pants with one leg,
or realising that you couldn't move
after waking up
from a nap.
That's what we call a twisted waist.
There are often patients
who experience stuffy chests,
dizziness,
or bedridden due to leg pain
due to misalignment of the spine.
As the saying goes,
it takes a hundred days for the bone
to knit and tendons to heal.
Some people might look like
they've recovered
after lying down for some time.
But in reality,
it became the root of other illnesses.
Ever since smartphones
and laptops
became essential parts of our lives,
even as an extension
of our organs,
I could conclude
that spondylosis
would be a common occurrence
in the future.
However, such illness
can be treated easily
with our methods.
As long as you give us enough time,
I can restore your spines
to their factory setting.
Ms Dong, you should sit down
and teach us.
Thank you.
However, chairs with wheels
underneath them
shouldn't be used.
Chairs like these
are one of the main reasons
of waist and
and spinal issues.
Chinese characters are very meaningful.
I wish to talk about the character
"Zuo".
Tian Zhen,
can you come here
and write it down?
Okay.
Look.
The character "Zuo"
has two people
sitting on top of the earth.
Why are there two people?
To balance things out.
Why must it be on top of the earth?
Because it needs to be sturdy.
For chairs with wheels like these,
we need to use the strength
of our waist
to prevent it from moving.
But when we sit on it
and wish to move from here
to there,
it requires us
to have strong core strength.
What if you don't have
strong core strength?
What will you use then?
You'll use this part.
This is what we refer
to as lumbar rotation.
It's this part.
This will cause
the spine to be misaligned easily.
So, for my sake,
I think it's better
to teach you guys while standing.
So, who has
waist issues
among you all?
All of you?
Ms Dong, me.
Okay.
Tell me then.
Over here?
Why are all these things still here?
Who are you? What do you need?
We'll be renovating the place soon.
We're here to take measurements.
What measurements?
I'm not talking to you.
Take me the person in charge.
Wait.
Person in charge? That's me.
Let me see.
What is this?
I'm the person in charge here.
Hello. It's like this.
Mr Liu told us
to renovate the place.
-Renovate the place?
-That's right.
I even brought the contract here.
Please take a look.
What about this?
Please wait here for a moment.
I'll call Mr Liu.
Okay.
Let's go and take a look.
Wait here.
Take a break for now.
Guys, take a break.
Liu,
are you using the classroom
for
other purposes?
That's right.
I was just planning
to tell you about it.
It's like this. I wish to renovate
the classroom.
After that, I'll rent it out.
That's different from
what we agreed upon.
(Professor, you need to understand
my feelings too.)
Back then, I lent you the place
so that we could
cooperate
and create a win-win situation.
(But you're uninterested in
the TCM industrial park)
(and unwilling to join us.)
You see,
my capability and capital
is limited.
Besides,
I need to provide for
my family
and the employees in my company.
I have to be responsible for them.
(It's tough to make a living nowadays.)
(If I do this, at least
I can collect some rent.)
You know this too. I'm passionate
toward TCM too.
But my dear friend,
this might sound harsh,
but we can't make a living
with sentiment alone.
(That's why I could only rent it out)
(after renovating it.)
I have to rent the dorm out too
if it's possible.
You understand?
Fine then.
What about this?
So,
you three can wait outside
for the time being.
Let me deal with them first.
-Alright.
-Thank you.
Guys.
Please.
Ms Dong, it's like this.
For the hands-on technique class,
we have to suspend it for now.
Guys, listen up.
The apprentice class
will be suspended for the time being.
I'll notify you guys
when our class reopens.
Charge!
Okay. Break.
Ms Dong just told us
not to sit on this chair.
Only for a while.
What's going on?
Why are we having a sudden break?
I think everything's fine.
Don't worry.
My father will deal with it.
Tou!
Come here.
-Hurry up.
-Be careful.
What?
For this year's Qixi Festival,
they'll hold a lantern party
at the old street.
Initially, we had class.
Since God has given us
an excellent chance
by suspending our class,
why don't we head there
and enjoy ourselves?
You...
You should've told me
about this earlier.
I heard
that we could even rent Hanfu there.
We should rent some Hanfu
and take some pictures
to commemorate the festival.
Who knows? Maybe this is our last class.
Tou Tou,
don't jinx it.
Touch wood.
Meng Meng.
They're heading to the Qixi Festival
lantern party.
Do you want to join them?
But don't we need to apply for leave
from Mr Ren if we wish
to attend the event?
What leave?
-Mr Ren suspended the class.
-Yeah.
We don't even know
where the next class will be held at.
-Yeah.
-We should enjoy ourselves while we can.
That's right.
Let's go.
It's fun.
There are all kinds of games there.
And, they'll sell your
favourite food too.
I'll go there with you.
Do you want to join them?
Okay.
Why are you guys still standing there?
Go and pack your things.
Let's go.
Hurry up!
Rebecca,
you should come with us
to the Qixi Festival lantern party.
No, thanks. I'm not interested.
I advise you guys not to attend it.
Although we have a holiday,
we still have curfews.
Aren't you afraid that someone
might wreck the place?
Someone needs to
keep an eye on the place.
What? Do you want to defend
this place with your life?
I suggest you join us
so that you won't receive
any physical damage.
I'm not afraid.
Even if I do sustain damage,
Ms Dong will cure me.
Fine.
Later, we'll have dinner
at 7pm. Remember to
keep an eye on the group chat.
Okay? 7pm.
Remember, it's 7pm.
Don't forget.
Isn't this adorable?
You want that?
I'll get it for you.
Mister, how much does it cost?
Mister, I'll pay for it. Scan my code.
Thank you, Mr Tian Zhen.
I'll get it for you.
Give me another one.
Here I go.
Tou, you are terrible at this.
-You scared me. What?
-Give them to me.
-Can you do it?
-Here you go.
He got it!
Not bad at all.
Do you even know how to play the game?
Meng Meng,
I'm not very good at this.
However, I'm great at
playing claw machines.
If you want a plush toy,
I can get you
the toy you want.
It's hard to say.
We can do it too.
What are you
saying?
-You want to play?
-Yeah.
I'm good at this. Come.
It's impossible.
Listen, I'll get it on my first try.
You're just wasting your money.
That's impossible. Look.
Let me show you.
Senior,
I don't think I can do that.
(You own many companies
in the tertiary industry.)
Is it that hard for me
to get a classroom?
That's not the hard part.
The hard part is to pacify the people.
You see, if I'm giving you
what you want now,
what should I do
when other people ask me
for the same thing?
If I don't give it to them,
I'll be biased.
(You and I are from the same sect.)
(Just one report letter)
(is enough to land me in trouble.)
I thought you promised
Fellow Zhang
that your academy would help us out
if we were in trouble?
Now, the apprentice class
is in a pickle here.
How do you plan to resolve the issue?
Me?
At most, I can hold one,
two,
or even three seminars for you.
(But now, you're asking me
for a classroom.)
And, you'll be using it
for quite a few years.
The thing is,
you're not paying rent for it.
How can I explain myself
to the higher-ups?
What about this?
For the sake of your apprentice class,
I'll sacrifice my career.
I'll resign
(and be the class teacher)
(for the apprentice class.)
I'll be thick-skinned and go out
to ask for donations.
What do you think?
Stop your pointless chatter.
Fine.
I'll think of something myself.
Your lot
is the best out of all.
That's all?
Is this a good thing or a bad thing?
-I didn't get it.
-Yeah. Tell us the details.
-Is it good or bad?
-Late bloomer.
How late is late?
According to how
modern people calculate age,
it'll be around 60 years old.
60 years old?
That's pretty good.
People always seek out
senior TCM practitioners.
That's not it.
Both of my parents
made a name for themselves
at a young age.
But I'm only making a name
for myself at 60?
Do you think that's appropriate?
Yeah.
Why not? I think it's good enough
to make a name for yourself.
Look at me.
I'll stay like this
for the rest of my life.
I'm the same even when I'm 80.
Are you trying
to console me?
I don't think so.
Let's check out the other stalls.
Alright.
-Let's check them out.
-They're selling food.
-Meng Meng, let's go.
-Let's go.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
Let me ask you something.
Are you a human or a robot?
Sir, what other questions do you have?
It's fine. Thank you.
One of them
is a late bloomer
while the other one is a prodigy.
What should we do now?
I just feel apologetic
toward Ms Dong.
You always led a reclusive life.
Now,
you're here.
But we don't even have a classroom
for you to teach them.
Yeah, it's all my fault.
I should've expected this to happen
when I severed my ties
with them.
Actually, they're not obliged
to help us out
for free.
Businessmen
value profit over righteousness.
That's a hasty generalization.
There are many
righteous businessmen too.
Master,
you always told me
that if I have an idea,
everything will fall into place.
I had this idea
for a long time.
Why isn't anyone
giving me a classroom?
You see,
that only works
when you're Buddha.
You still have a long way to go.
You're right.
You see,
knowledge and action
should go hand in hand.
From realising
the righteousness of the event
to the completion of the event,
everything else in between
acts as your trial.
God is giving you an ordeal
called The Dignity Ordeal.
Master, you're right.
Master, I'll be honest with you.
In the past, I didn't think
that this industry was that tough.
But now, it's...
Think about it.
Throughout your career,
you were talented
and you had academic qualifications.
And,
you had elders like us
backing you up.
Of course you had a smooth journey.
You're right.
Now,
I'm old.
I'm afraid I won't be able
to back you up anymore.
I'm afraid you need to back me up
in the future.
Dad, such chatter is meaningless.
Now, we need to figure out a way
to resolve this issue.
Yeah.
Ms Dong,
I'm truly sorry.
We invited you all the way here,
however,
we don't even have a place
for you to teach them.
That's fine.
When we decide
to take the righteous path,
we have to put in much more effort
than taking the back door.
God will test you
repeatedly
to see
whether you're truly sincere
in taking this path.
If you can pass God's test
every time without changing your goal,
you'll achieve what you wish for.
In my opinion,
this isn't even
an ordeal for you.
You're
an academician.
You published books and
made a name for yourself.
But people like us?
It's quite difficult for us
to pass our legacy
to the next generation.
In Taoism,
masters will look for
their own disciples.
I agreed to join your class
not because to help you out.
I'm helping myself out.
I was thinking
that I'll encounter a disciple
who's a kindred spirit
if I teach enough classes.
Maybe that person is willing
to inherit our legacy
without changing anything.
(The prescriptions and remedies
used in this drama)
(are referenced from relevant
traditional Chinese medicine books)
(Do not use without medical advice)
(End of Episode 12)