Met you by Gong Wuyue
♫ The moment you pass by my side ♫
♫ Smiling ♫
♫ You entered my heart ♫
♫ How happy the two of us are under the clear sky ♫
♫ The promise we once made ♫
♫ Is like a love song echoing in the bottom of the heart ♫
♫ Laughter replaces silence ♫
♫ Like dazzling fireworks ♫
♫ Meeting you like this, getting closer unintentionally ♫
♫ The silence melts away, because I can't help it ♫
♫ It's like I feel a connection with you,  ♫
♫ But I'm unwilling to trust it easily ♫
♫ Meeting you like this has filled me with surprises ♫
♫ So deep in my memory is our mutual connection ♫
♫ In my life, ♫
♫ I have been able to meet you ♫
[MEETING YOU]
Xiarui!
Where are you going?
I...am staying...
I am staying outside for two days.
Staying outside?
I just saw you.
Oh my goodness! Are you staying in
with that boyfriend of yours?
My god, girl!
Do you want everyone to hear it?
How about this?
You help me to keep this a secret.
I will pay for all your milk tea
for this month. Okay?
But, it's almost the end of the month.
I will also pay for next month, alright?
Now that's more like it!
I will help you carry your luggage.
But, let me tell you.
There are things you need be
mindful of when living together.
I read an online comment
from someone saying that
staying together is one
of the reasons why couple break up.
You better be careful.
I treat you for milk tea
and you treat me like this?
I am not cursing you.
I am worried about you.
Also, what was his explanation on the photos two days ago?
I saw it with my eyes. You went crazy
when you saw photos of him
dancing with other people.
Yang Yufei?
Oh, no. You misunderstood.
That's just a misunderstanding.
- Slowly.
- Okay.
- Watch your hand.
- Alright.
This is the last box.
Did I bring too much stuff?
How can it be? Not much.
But, we need to move it upstairs later.
Do you want to move it now or later?
Let's move it now.
But... suddenly, I don't have energy.
No energy at all.
Then, do you want to rest for awhile?
I think I probably need to recharge.
Recharge.
What are you doing?
Oh no. Oh no.
I am about to shut down. I am done for.
Low battery.
Alright, fully recharged!
[EPISODE 22]
[LET'S STOP BEING FRIENDS WITH THEM]
Xiarui, are you finished?
Still not done?
I am done!
- You are done?
- Yeah.
Let me introduce to you.
This pile over here are clothes
that are okay to wear again
since they're not dirty.
I can just wear them again.
Over there are my pants.
Also, for these jackets,
you can grab them on the go.
As for shoes, I will just
slip on the ones I see.
As for these books,
they are neatly put here.
Look, grab one of it and there's
hospitality management.
Isn't it convenient?
I hung up the clothes here
to prevent wrinkling.
Over here are my beauty products.
Am I an expert in storage?
As long as you are comfortable,
then it's fine.
Nanxi, Nanxi.
Boss Yi wants me
to bring you along to work tomorrow.
I don't know what he is planning.
I will accompany you.
It's not you accompanying me.
He wants to meet you.
If I go there, it's considered
me accompanying you.
Come over here.
You are getting good at sweet talk lately.
Who taught you this?
Have you finished memorizing the text?
I am going to memorize it now, Nanxi.
Nothing, nothing.
I have helped you settle
the university forum issue.
Had it not been for Boss Yi intervening,
I would have blacklisted Yang Yufei.
Yang Yufei?
What does this
have anything to do with her?
Why are you taking it out on her?
Isn't she the one who uploaded the post?
Of course, it isn't her.
She is also a victim.
If she didn't upload the post,
then who did it?
It was her classmates,
who like spreading baseless rumors.
When Yang Yufei was in school,
didn't she have a crush on Nanxi?
Yes, she did.
But, Yang Yufei was not involved in it.
Also, I was in that class too.
You are spying on Nanxi?
How is this spying?
This is considered as caring, okay?
Moreover, Yang Yufei had contacted me,
to tell me that she will
help me delete the post.
The innocent need not do anything.
Just letting it to is the best response.
Didn't you have a crush on Yang Yufei?
What happened all of a sudden?
I, Binzi, am a person with principles.
I always focus on facts, not people.
Let me tell you.
Be careful with your words.
You might lose the people you love.
Okay.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh my goodness.
How is he so handsome?
I want to add him on WeChat.
I see what you did there, Boss Yi.
Without him here,
your business wouldn't run.
I was wondering why
you asked Nanxi to come here.
It's because you wanted him
to be the mascot
to increase customer turnover.
I disagree with that.
I gave him the best spot in the cafe. Why?
So that he can appreciate your charm
while you work.
If you don't believe me,
ask him if he likes it or not.
Nanxi didn't even want to
come here to begin with.
You really are a fox.
Good with words, too.
You are misusing the idioms again.
Why does your Nanxi
have to be so attractive?
Look at them.
To show you my appreciation,
I will teach you the core technique
of making coffee, okay?
Deal!
It's a rare opportunity
to see our boss perform.
Is the camera focused?
Yes, of course.
Let me see, let me see.
What do you think?
Was it worth your tuition fees?
Master, please accept me as your disciple.
Stand up.
Hurry up and deliver the coffee
to the customer.
Wait, let me do a closeup.
Put it here.
When did you start this hobby?
As the only full-time employee here,
I have 3128 fans, you know?
My fan base is even larger than Nanxi's.
Then, you can do a live broadcast.
Don't people do
live mukbang broadcast lately?
You can do a live broadcast
just drinking coffee.
Good idea.
Let me take another picture.
Wow, you even put a filter on the picture.
Are the two of you done?
The coffee will get cold
if you don't stop talking about it.
Okay, okay, okay.
Whose salary should I deduct
if customers complain?
No, no, no.
Wow, if a person is handsome,
he looks good in every photo,
no matter it was taken.
Hey, what kind of photo is this?
This angle doesn't do justice to his face.
You still think he looks good?
He was just sitting down while
I took these. Why don't you try?
Okay then, I will try. Go away.
Oh my gosh.
Stretch your legs out.
Stretch them.
Pose for the camera. A handsome pose.
Yes, that's it!
Let me see, let me see, let me see.
Take it.
This photo looks better.
Hi, can you send us a copy of the photo?
Oh, I have a lot of photos. Do you...
No, no, no thanks.
Follow me. Follow me.
Nanxi!
Huh? What?
What is happening?
Nanxi, Nanxi!
Did you just disconnect the internet?
In the future, the internet will be
off at eleven.
This..This is not a university dormitory!
Why did you disconnect the internet?
I am playing games! They will report me!
What time do you usually sleep?
When I am in the dormitory, I only sleep
when they disconnect the internet.
What time do you go to sleep now?
Now--
I slept a little late.
This is the second time this week that I saw you staying up till morning,
playing games.
It's not because I like this game
that I played it.
I played it just to kill time.
Kill time?
Didn't you stay up late, too?
I was watching a documentary
to get some inspiration.
So that's why I...
So...
So, that's why you stayed up late
playing games...
...just to accompany me?
I am going to sleep.
Xiarui.
I am sorry. It's my fault.
I disconnected the internet
without asking you.
So, you are just going to say sorry?
Or why don't I just reconnect
the internet for you?
There is no need.
Unless you play a game with me.
Can you?
Alright, let's play.
You laughed.
- I didn't.
- Give it to me.
- You laughed.
- I didn't.
- My turn.
You laughed. Come, come, come.
I don't want to.
I want to draw on you.
♫ Passing by the roads
you walked step by step ♫
- You laughed!
- I didn't.
Why are you still fooling around?
♫ Being lonely among the traffic lights ♫
Are you this brave now?
♫ Forgetting too many sad memories ♫
You can't draw me.
♫ My heart is now conflicted ♫
Nanxi drew too much on your face.
Who knew that this marker pen stain
would be hard to wash off?
Let me tell you.
Nanxi's face is no better than mine.
There's still a mole near his mouth.
I feel better when I think about it.
I don't know if it's still a good idea
for both of you to live together.
Hey, is Chubby Cheng helping
Si Bo to go after you?
It looked like Si Bo asked him
personally for help.
Or maybe it's like what they said.
They just happened to talk about me.
He's too stupid.
He's too slow.
He's...he's too insensitive.
Anybody could tell there was
a reason why Si Bo kept talking about you.
He is not just insensitive,
but hard-headed as wood.
You already gave him so many hints.
How come he still don't get it?
Yeah, it's been so long.
I thought that he would
understand me by now.
You also know that we girls
mature earlier than boys.
I thought I could wait.
Three years, five years, ten years.
But now, even when someone pursues me,
he still isn't bothered by it
and just goes with it.
I don't think I can't wait any longer.
It's also my fault.
I was so busy moving out that
I had no time to teach him.
Seriously.
It's okay.
Actually, that's his own matter.
Good thing I am busy recently.
Busy with rehearsals. My first TV show started script reading.
I don't need to think of
all those messy things.
Finally others will get to
see my precious friend.
Congratulations!
What are you guys talking about?
You both look happy.
I will go back to rehearsals first.
Don't... don't... Shu.
Why do you leave when you see me?
Are you still mad at me?
It's has nothing to do with you.
You...Why are you avoiding me recently?
Stop interrupting her rehearsals, alright?
How about this?
Tonight, both of you come to our house.
I haven't treated you both to a meal
after I moved out.
Tonight, Nanxi will be cooking.
Let's have a... a housewarming party.
What do you say?
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
The post was really taken down.
Could it be that
I misunderstood her before?
Binzi, seriously.
Xiarui already said that it was
a misunderstanding.
Not only you don't trust her,
but you also didn't sell any coffee
and was absent for half a day.
I would have forgotten about this matter.
I haven't deducted your salary
for your absence.
Don't overdo it, Boss Yi.
I am just helping Xiarui
clear her name.
Hmm, how generous of you.
This was just a simple misunderstanding.
It became more complicated
after you butted in.
Then, did I really misunderstand Yufei?
Hey, your general
has created a chance for you.
Boss Yi, did you do something
behind my back?
Young man. This is me helping you.
What do you want to drink?
One cup of latte, no sugar.
Alright.
Who was the one who swore
not to sell me any coffee a few days ago?
Yufei. It's my fault.
I... I knew you were the one who took down
the post about Xiarui.
An apology is not enough.
You need to show me some sincerity.
Boss Yi, are you done with
the six cups of expresso that I ordered?
Coming!
Here you go, boss! Your coffee.
Do you really want Binzi
to finish all of these in one go?
Didn't you say that he wants
to prove his sincerity?
Drink all of these in one go?
Maybe you should forget it.
There's a proverb that says A real man is flexible.
Right?
Sometimes, a man should back down
when he can.
Forget it, forget it.
Don't stop me, boss.
I will drink it.
I, Binzi, always take responsibility
for my actions.
What's right, is right.
What's wrong, is wrong.
What a real man.
What a real man, indeed.
I didn't ask you to drink them all.
I am done.
Anyhow, Yufei.
I was wrong.
I shouldn't have treated you poorly
before finding out the truth.
Alright, I forgive you.
Really?
- Not satisfied?
- Satisfied, satisfied!
Boss Yi, I have class later.
I'll leave first.
Bye!
Goodbye.
You're welcome.
Alright, stop peeping!
Binzi, you already apologize
and confessed to her.
Why are you still acting?
Go and wash the cups!
Who confessed?
Nothing, nothing.
However, let me tell you,
these will be deducted from your salary.
Fine, I am in a good mood today.
Go ahead and deduct my salary.
But, I'd like to ask you something.
My heartbeat should be faster
after drinking these expressos.
How come I still feel so calm?
Well, maybe someone has secretly
add water into the expresso.
Boss Yi, you are the best.
Go away, go away!
I am worried that you lost your sanity
while apologizing.
Since you already added water,
you can't ask me to pay for six cups.
- The most is two cups.
- No, can't do!
Three cups!
Deal!
- Xiarui.
- Yes?
I have been wanting to ask you something.
Ask ahead.
Cohabitating... emm... no...
How's life staying in the same place?
Is it good?
You can't be serious.
Both of you have such good life now.
We have completely different habits
and schedules.
I like to sleep in through the morning.
He already woke me up at six am.
She just placed her stuff everywhere.
It's so messy that she put it outside.
Also, he especially likes to hide stuff.
I can never find it
whenever I need to use it.
Do you know that
she doesn't like to clean up?
He can mop for 800 times in one day.
I even think that
the floor wouldn't get so dirty easily.
She forgets to close the door
when she uses the toilet.
Also, he walks around without a sound.
It scared me in the middle of night
so much that I almost had a heart attack.
Well, from my perception, I don't think
it's suitable for you to live together.
Seeing this, I think that you will
break up sooner or later.
Impossible!
Come, Shu. Have some.
You only gave her vegetables?
Thank you.
Shu, you don't need to thank me.
I am not used to you thanking me.
You will get used to it.
Don't we have ice-cream in the fridge?
We have all flavours.
Later, you can eat any of it as you like.
I've been trying to quit sugar recently.
You guys just go ahead.
Shu, you don't need to lose weight.
You will become too thin if you do.
Xiarui, why did you kick me?
Just eat your food, alright?
And don't talk with your mounth full.
I'll go wash some more vegetables.
I'll help you.
Just eat!
Do you still remember Xiao Bailing
from our dormitory?
Xiao Bailing?
- Yes.
Her mother wants her to go matchmaking.
Oh my goodness.
What's the rush?
She hasn't graduated yet.
Also, Xiao Bailing is pretty.
Why the rush for matchmaking?
How is being pretty related
to matchmaking?
Shu, will your family also
arrange matchmaking for you?
How ridiculous!
It's ridiculous?
It's ridiculous!
People should be together because of love.
You see, for matchmaking,
everyone just state their conditions.
They compare candidates
with each other like in the market.
I don't think it's ridiculous.
The objective is there
along with the conditions.
If it's works, fine. If it doesn't,
just split up. I think it's good.
Shu, how can you be thinking like this?
Let's stop talking
about the matchmaking.
Aren't we celebrating
us moving in together?
- Come, come, come.
- Xiarui, wait.
Shu, I think that it's not good
for you to think so.
As a long time friend since a young age,
I...I should help you,
give you some advice.
Falling in love isn't something you trade
with others.
You need to find someone that you love.
That way you'll be happy.
How will you know that if I love him,
he also loves me back?
Shu, you have someone
that you love?
Who's the guy?
Do we know him?
Can't we just eat?
If we can't finish the food,
I will put all of it into your mouth.
Just eat!
Your saliva is all over the table.
Just continue eating.
Eat, eat, eat.
No, why are both of you
attacking me today?
Just eat.
Xiarui, I have to leave first.
I will see you tomorrow.
I will send you off.
Why are you leaving so soon?
There's still plenty of food.
She's walking home alone. It's dangerous.
Aren't you sending her off?
He doesn't have to.
I can walk home alone.
What are you doing?
Do you want me to beat you up?
Go. Hurry up. Pick up the pace.
Shu!
Oh my goodness.
Oh my goodness, oh my goodness.
Being their friend is tiring.
I am mentally tired.
Let's stop being friends with them.
We should have done so earlier.
We should stop bothering
with their issues.
We can't intervene.
Shu, Shu.
Shu, I want to talk to you.
Talk about what?
I think what you did today
was unacceptable.
What did I do?
You can lash out on me.
But, you can't do it to Nanxi and Xiarui.
It's hard for us to meet up together.
The meet up turned sour because of us.
What you meant to say is that
I am the party pooper, is it?
I will just open up the truth.
No matter what I said, you'll be angry.
I might as well tell you the truth.
You want me to be honest with you?
Okay, let me tell you.
Cheng Erluo, do you know that
you're a hopeless idiot?
I am angry but that's not the reason for my anger.
Everytime, you don't even
why I am angry.
You always think that I am
being unreasonable, right?
How could it be not?
I kept on thinking
about my mistakes recently.
I just didn't come and fetch you.
I already told you I was training.
In your eyes, I was easily provoked by
small matters, is it?
Let me tell you.
I am furious, but it's not because of
you missing out on picking me up.
The reason is because when I tried to distance myself from you
you kept on bonding with me.
When I tried to bond with you,
you ditched me cruelly.
I am angry because no matter what I said,
you being a blockhead will never get it!
What have I done wrong?
When did I ditch you cruelly?
Just like this!
If you want to quarrel, then fine.
Why did you become like Xiarui?
Xiarui, Xiarui.
Are you okay?
Stomachache.
Stomachache?
Yes.
Wait here.
Oh my gosh.
Come, drink this brown sugar soup.
Why do I need to drink this?
Don't ask any question. Just drink it.
I don't want to drink it.
No, you have to.
Have one more sip.
Come on.
Drink more.
It's good for you.
I don't want to drink it, Nanxi.
Okay, okay, okay.
Lay down.
What... what are you doing?
Why are you giving me a heating pad?
I asked Shu.
She said that this
is more comfortable.
If you are still in pain,
let's call her and ask her again.
What did you consult her on?
It's on.
It's on...that thing.
Well, don't your 'relatives' come
and visit you every month?
I asked her what can a man...do
during that time.
No... Nanxi.
I do not...
but I need to go to the toilet.
Come and sit down.
Let's take another sip.
Nanxi, it's not that.
It's not because of my period.
It's probably because of
the expired ice-cream.
You...You got a stomachache?
Yes.
When did you prepare
all of these things?
Tell me, is there anything else?
I just remembered that I still
haven't completed my assignment.
I am going to do so now.
The Woodie is getting embarrassed.
No.
Come on, it's still not good enough?
Three meters isn't enough for each floor.
Three meters is still not enough?
The height for public building
should be 3.9 meters for each floor.
There's a thirty meter difference.
You need to redo this building plan.
Oh, he's right.
What were you thinking
throughout the day?
You put only three meters for each floor.
Are you constructing an apartment?
It's easier to count that way.
Didn't you know there's a thing
called a calculator?!
How can you get into Binhai University
with this brain?
Don't you dare insult me!
You got chips on my building plan!
If you are so good, show Nanxi
your building plan!
I-I-I haven't finish drawing mine.
Nanxi, have you finish drawing yours?
Let us have a look.
We want to learn from it.
This is so meticulous!
Nanxi, you're a genius in architecture!
My graduation project might not be
as excellent as this.
Looks like you are a shoe in
for first place in midterm.
It's marvelous!
Senior, what are you doing here?
Professor Gu asked me to help out
with the design competition.
I happened to pass by.
So, I came in.
I heard that this year's
architecture design competition
will be held in our campus.
Also, I heard that
the winner will get to participate
in an exchange program in Italy.
Why both of you
knew everything?
How is this a secret?
It's nothing!
Are you interested
in taking part?
Hao Tian, I think both of us
can give it a try.
What if we got lucky
and we got the first place.
We will then be popular in campus.
No way. I was already badly
abused by Nanxi at home.
I don't want to get
humiliated in public again.
Come here to help me have a look.
Why did you give up easily?
What about you, Nanxi?
Interested in taking part?
Thanks, senior. But, I am not interested.
Your talent should be seen by the public.
Architecture isn't a competition.
It's okay
since the deadline for sign ups
is still a long way.
If you change your mind, go
and look for Professor Gu.
Thanks, senior!
Are you going to Cafe Yami?
Senior, you also know Cafe Yami?
Everyone knows it.
I heard that the coffee
and the environment there is good.
I happened to be free today.
Can you show me the way
so that I can try the coffee there?
Come, have a look.
How is it?
Eight points!
Not bad, Xiarui!
You have mastered
coffee art during the whole afternoon.
Looks like aside from having an
excellent sense of taste,
you have skills too.
You are my top student.
Nanxi, is it pretty?
It's pretty.
You are not listening to
a professional opinion from the master.
But you are asking him?
Aside from looking at you passionately
and telling you
the drink is good.
The food is good.
What else can he do?
The drink is delicious and pretty.
Then, it's good enough.
Try my first creation.
Try it, try it.
Even though this coffee is
for you to practice,
you can't simply give it others.
Is it good?
It's good.
Are you listening to what I am saying?
I will also let Si Bo try it
and get his opinion.
Is my business still running?
Why so stingy?
Just deduct it from my salary.
Looks like it doesn't matter whether
I am the boss.
I think it's best to give
the WBC invitation to someone else.
WBC?
Invitation?
And he is bragging about it.
I can only brag
about it now.
Is this for real?
Let me have a look.
It's my fault, it's my fault. Let me see.
Have a good look.
Is this real or fake?
You... you really have a hidden talent.
Your master is in the
coffee business for many years.
I just happened to see
through that world.
What is WBC?
It's the World Barista Competition. This is an exclusive competition.
Baristas who made their debut
at the competition are geniuses.
You also know that I am a relaxed person.
I don't like being in the competition.
But, I went to the WBC a few times.
They learn from each other,
which creates a good enviornment.
This year, they organized
another competition in Jiangzhou.
They specifically asked me to participate.
I am still considering
whether to go or not.
That's being ungrateful.
Others are dying for this chance
and you're still hesitant to participate.
What a show off!
How about you take my place
in the competition?
Be the representative of our cafe.
What do you say?
Are you joking? How can I
participate in such grand competition?
Young lady, this competition
is an excellent opportunity
for youngsters to practice their skills.
If you want to be a top barista,
aside from skills, your mentality is also important.
Learn from the experts.
Meeting the masters will benefit you.
Wouldn't I embarrass you if I participate?
I told you,
I don't bother with trivalities of life.
Why should I be afraid
of being humiliated?
Why is it that your words
don't sound encouraging at all?
Xiarui. Go and have a try.
No, this is a grand competition.
As a beginner,
isn't this a little too fast?
I believe in you.
But, I lack self-confidence.
Then I'll go with you.
To Jiangzhou?
Yes, to Jiangzhou.
Nanxi said he will go with you.
You should believe in yourself.
Am I making a hasty decision?
I now regret it a little bit.
What should I do
for the preliminary, Nanxi?
Timing and subtitles brought to you by Nice To Meet You Team@ Viki.com
♫ The sound of the school's release bell is always so wonderful ♫
♫ The story will be the same tomorrow ♫
♫ You wear your earbuds ♫
♫ I push the bicycle to wait for you ♫
♫ No need to use language, we still feel the warmth ♫
♫ Waiting for the next vacation ♫
♫ Waiting for the next trip ♫
♫ Waiting for the next crossroad where I will present you a letter ♫
♫ The summer after graduation ♫
♫ Inside the tree hole next to the sports field ♫
♫ Store the memories I have of you ♫
♫ You are the most beautiful scenery of my memory ♫
♫ Cicadas sleep on the desks ♫
♫ The textbooks are imprinted on my face ♫
♫ The teacher's chalk ♫
♫ I am being punished to stand against the wall ♫
♫ Your eyes watch me, secretly laughing ♫
♫ The sound of the school's release bell is always so wonderful ♫
♫ The story will be the same tomorrow ♫
♫ You wear your earbuds ♫
♫ I push the bicycle to wait for you ♫
♫ The story will be the same tomorrow ♫
♫ You wear your earbuds ♫
♫ I push the bicycle to wait for you ♫
♫ No need to use language, we still feel the warmth ♫
♫ Waiting for the next vacation ♫
♫ Waiting for the next trip ♫
♫ Waiting for the next crossroad where I will present you a letter
♫ The summer after graduation ♫