Timing and subtitles brought to you by Nice To Meet You Team@ Viki.com
Met you by Gong Wuyue
♫ The moment you pass by my side ♫
♫ Smiling ♫
♫ You entered my heart ♫
♫ How happy the two of us are under the clear sky ♫
♫ The promise we once made ♫
♫ Is like a love song echoing in the bottom of the heart ♫
♫ Laughter replaces silence ♫
♫ Like dazzling fi reworks ♫
♫ Meeting you like this, getting closer unintentionally ♫
♫ The silence melts away, because I can't help it ♫
♫ It's like I feel a connection with you,  ♫
♫ But I'm unwilling to trust it easily ♫
♫ Meeting you like this has filled me with surprises ♫
♫ So deep in my memory is our mutual connection ♫
♫ In my life, ♫
♫ I have been able to meet you ♫
[Meeting You]
Why are you waiting for me here?
No way.
You prepared all these?
Sit down.
Try my cooking.
Smells good?
Good.
Try one by one, try this first.
Is it delicious? Is it delicious?
- It's delicious.
- Really?
Really.
Let me get you a bowl of soup.
Just a minor injury.
Let me have a look.
Really just a minor injury.
Be obedient.
In the future, I will cook.
You don't have to.
I-I-I will be more careful.
Does it hurt?
No, it doesn't.
Nevermind.
Come.
Let me see.
How was it ?
N-N-Nan Xi.
[EP 24]
[IMPERFECT PERFECTION]
Xiarui. How can you just refuse like this?
Although it's quite cool this way.
But you should have discussed with us.
What's there to discuss?
I think it's not about
what to discuss.
Because of Nanxi, you give up your dream.
Isn't this stupid?
I'm just not going to Italy.
I'm staying to make Yami shine,
isn't that a good thing too?
Yami has me.
With my Weibo and live broadcast fans. Enough for a living.
Don't worry about it.
But isn't there any other way ?
Boss Yi. Can't we just look for that, that...
What is it called?
Wang... Wang Wei To.
Tell him,
we should discuss again.
I asked someone from the WBC.
He left Binhai a long time ago.
He is probably in Milan now.
Okay. I know that you all care about me.
I'm just not going to Italy.
Not like I'm giving up on making coffee.
Moreover, our Boss Yi
is as good as Wang Wei To.
Look at our Xiarui, all grown up.
What she says really makes sense.
That's right.
Don't tell Nanxi about this.
Their department recently
has a design competition.
Everyone is persuading
him to participate in the competition.
Don't disturb him at this time.
He is troubled.
Didn't Nanxi go to Jiangzhou to find you?
Why didn't you both came back together?
He said there was something urgent
in college, and needed to go back first.
Nanxi.
We were talking about you.
Have a look.
What is this?
School introduction and admission guide.
School? What school is this?
Why can't I understand anything?
This is Mr. Umberto's training school.
Besides, I've registered
you for language class.
- How did you know?
- I didn't tell him anything.
You didn't even have time to tell.
I don't want to go to Italy.
What if we go together.
Sir.
Please wait.
What's the matter?
Sorry to disturb you.
That girl is my girlfriend, Xiarui.
She loves coffee very much.
Please reconsider again.
This is my email.
I'll write it for you.
You can reach me anytime.
Okay, sure.
Thank you.
[Dear Nanxi, Here's the introduction of
the institute that I am in.]
[Take a look and see if there is any problem. ]
[Hope I can see you and your friend in Italy.]
Professor Gu.
What is it?
Professor Gu, first place
for the architectural design
gets to go to Milan as exchange student?
You're talking about the
College Student's Design competition
that will be held soon?
Correct.
Yes.
Our school established a cooperation with
their School of Architecture.
The winner will not only
get our college qualification,
like in the previous years
But now he/she can also go to Milan
as an exchange student for a year.
And you have to ensure that
during your third year of studies
you have to come back for the graduation
project and graduation thesis report.
Understood.
I want to participate.
Didn't you always reject the competition?
Why all of a sudden,
you changed your mind?
Because I want to go to Milan.
Nanxi is really something.
Does nothing at all but once he makes a move makes us single people look like a fool.
You are the fool.
But the move that you made,
I really admire.
You really want to
participate in the competition??
Didn't you say design,
is not meant for competition.
But it could keep both of us together.
Aren't we together now?
There's us.
And dreams.
But I still don't want you to go.
Once we are there,
we have to face lots of new things.
New language, new country,
new environment. And a bunch of people
that we don't even know,
that we have to get to know too.
Everything will be different. I don't
want that because of me--
Don't worry.
With you, I'm not afraid.
I can't take it anymore.
Even this coffee can't wash out
the sweetnesss in my tooth now.
Binzi, how about you give me another
Italian espresso.
I'll have a bitter one to neutralize this.
Boss Yi. When did our cafe have
art selection service?
That was the coffee Xiarui
made during the rematch.
I'm ready to sell it at our shop.
Let everyone taste it.
Isn't it little whale?
Why is it that little whale met big whale?
You have to ask our Xiarui.
This is too much.
I need a cup of coffee too.
The best would be Chinese herbs flavour.
Just needs to be bitter, nothing else.
It seems like coffee can no
longer neutralize me.
I'm leaving. I'm going to play basketball. Let's have dinner together later.
Are we going together?
Why not...
You are hiding something from me again?
Nothing, nothing, nothing.
You may leave, you may leave,
you may leave. We'll talk later.
Okay then.
You try this.
Delicious.
Not bad. Let's call it a day.
Sure, let's stop here today.
Si bo. I have a question.
Always wanted to ask you.
Say it.
There are 14 people in our team.
They are pretty talented too.
Why do you have so much confidence in me?
And are willing to spare time
training in school with me?
This question
is not easy to answer.
Shu. How did you know that
I just finished my training?
Have a meal?
No problem.
Then wait for me.
- Shu?
- Yes.
Asking to have dinner together tonight.
Si Bo,
Let's go together tonight.
If you guys are having dinner,
I won't be joining.
No, I've always wanted to
invite you to have dinner together.
It's not easy to pick a date, right?
Moreover, Shu is not an outsider, right?
You know Nanxi too.
- Nanxi is going as well?
- Probably?
We've made an appointment to
have dinner together since lunch.
To celebrate Nanxi, signing up for
the design competition.
Nanxi already signed up?
That's right.
Why did he change his
mind all of a sudden?
Si Bo. It's either you ask Nanxi.
Or you just follow me.
I will tell you about it when we
are on the way. Let's go I'm so hungry.
Cheng Erluo. Practice went well today.
Just that.
The moment when you turn around.
You have to be fast.
- The step where my body turns?
- Right.
And when I'm backing up your shot
you must pay attention on--
Si Bo. What happened during the shot?
What happened during the shot?
You guys are eating here?
Yes.
I have never been here before.
But it looks pretty good.
Why?
Si Bo, have you been here before?
Once or twice.
Wherever you have been once or twice.
It should taste good.
Let's go.
I'm not going.
Shu could be waiting for you.
Cheng Erluo. I can answer your question now.
The reason why I'm helping
you out with your practice.
Not just hoping that you could
achieve good results in the C.U.B.A.
I also hope.
You can be a better Cheng Erluo.
Thank you, Si Bo.
I will definitely work hard.
Keep it up.
Are you really not going to eat?
Go.
Go ahead.
Then I'm going.
Keep it up.
Shu. Why are you alone?
Where is Xiarui?
Xiarui and Nanxi have
something going on tonight.
It's just the two of us.
If I'd knew I would have
brought Si Bo along.
The more people the merrier it is,
isn't it?
Did you see he was at the doorstep,
but turned around and left.
Did he mention why?
He did not. He just left.
Quite suddenly.
Maybe he had something all of a sudden.
He must be unlucky.
Because this place seems good.
Not like where Xiarui always brings us.
It's either skewer or the food stall.
I smell like lamb skewer.
Our Shu knows how to pick a good place.
Cheng Erluo.
I...
Actually, today I want to tell you...
Why are you so nervous?
Do you want to say something?
Is it…
The same thing that I'm guessing?
Guess what?
Isn't it just a meal?
My treat.
Leave it to me.
- Actually I...
- Actually I have a lot that
I want to tell you.
You first.
Si Bo has been helping
me with my practice recently?
A long time has passed.
Actually, he's quite nice.
Like just now.
Do you know what he said to me?
What did he say?
I hope you can become a
better Cheng Erluo.
You know how touched I was?
It's like the line of the idol
drama male lead.
If I were a girl I would have
fallen in love with him on the spot.
- Shu.
- I've thought about it for a long time.
This Si Bo usually
takes care of you.
If two of you have any misunderstanding
I, Cheng Erluo
will untie it all by myself.
Our boat of friendship can't
just turn over like that.
Friendship.
Yeah!
You see, look at me, how tough I am.
Si Bo is my good brother.
If there's something unhappy
between you two.
I'm between the both of you.
It's very hard for me.
Cheng Erluo.
Are we just friends?
Of course not.
Best friends.
Buddies.
Bestie.
Whichever it is.
What did you want to tell me?
Nothing. I'm not feeling well.
I'll go first.
Are you okay?
Waiter, pack it up, pack it up!
Shu.
Come in.
Why did you finish your meal this early?
How was it ?
Did you tell Cheng Erluo?
Is he very excited?
Until he couldn't speak a word?
I... didn't say anything.
Why?
Come in first.
Sit.
Why?
I knew you would ask me, so I came
here immediately from the restaurant.
What happened? Tell me.
I think
Cheng Erluo doesn't want
to be in a relationship right now.
I think I have to reconsider
our relationship.
Think? About what?
Did he bully you?
I'll teach him a lesson for you!
Please don't, Xiarui.
I came here just to tell you…
if you see him, please
don't tell him about this.
And don't tell Nanxi either.
Are you sure about this?
Growing up
I've been taken care of and
had everything organized by my parents.
Even had you protecting me at school.
My life seems a bit too smooth.
So smooth that I don't know what I like,
that I don't know what life has given me.
But whether if it's yours or
what you have in life, it's all yours.
It's not the same.
Just like how I grew up with
mom and dad behind the stage.
Like I should be an actor without a doubt.
Cheng Erluo has been by my
side since childhood.
I seem to have fallen for him,
as if it was the right thing to do.
Today he asked me, do we
even need to explain our relationship?
I was a little unclear at that time.
Do I like him, or am I used to him?
So I think I should think about it now.
But about what it? Of course you like him.
I hope so.
Xiarui, I'm back.
I better be going.
Promise me, don't say anything.
Oke, I won't.
- Okay.
- Nanxi, I'm leaving now.
- Bye bye.
Don't need to send me out.
What happened to Zhao Yishu?
She was…
Erm, nothing.
Are you tired today?
A little.
What?
Why?
Exhausted?
Nanxi.
Don't move. Let me hug you for a while.
Why? Are you using me as a charger?
Recovering blood and charge.
Shu was right.
You boys are childish.
Yes.
Yes, indeed.
Xiarui.
Are you tired from memorizing vocabulary?
Not tired.
I want to try my best.
Hand in hand. One step, two steps
three four steps, looking at the sky.
Looking at the stars
alligning into a line.
Shut up! Don't move!
Yufei!
It's me! It's me!
Yang Yufei!
Yufei, I didn't mean to yell at you.
It's okay now, okay?
I'm here.
- Don't go. Don't go!
- I won't go, I won't go.
I will not go. I'll just be here.
I'll stay with you.
I'm not going anywhere.
Erm, give me your phone.
This… is my number.
If you are going home alone
in the future, you just call me.
I will go with you, okay?
I'll always be with you.
You are
my friend.
I, Binzi won't let anyone bully my friend.
It's okay.
Are you feeling better?
Then I'll take you back.
Let's go.
Come.
I'll drive you home.
You can hold on to my clothes.
Let's go.
If you can't sit still then just
put your hands on me.
Rest assured.
I don't mean to take advantage of you.
I just think it's too dark,
I'm afraid to knock you off.
Actually today, I should've
sent that kid to the police station.
I'm telling you.
Not that I'm bragging.
What Ermei clan, Wudang clan,
Huashan clan?
I have no problem taking them down.
Ermei?
Isn't Ermei a female clan?
Doesn't matter male or female clan,
it's all written in the novels.
As long as you can beat bad guys,
catch thieves, then it's a good clan.
I'm fine, thank you.
I was just a little scared earlier.
Yufei, don't worry.
You don't need to be scared as long
as I'm here. And don't be too moved.
I'm simply a very righteous person.
Then…
Mr. righteous Egg Yolk Clan Schoolmate.
If you drive at this speed,
I'm not going to reach the dorm in time.
I'm just afraid you'll fall.
Or your bike couldn't speed up?
I really hate people provoking me!
Speeding up!
Your school is quite big.
University students are pretty happy.
Liubin, let me ask you a question.
Have you ever thought of taking the
university entrance exam again?
Forget it. I definitely can't.
Forget it. Forget it.
I remember your results
were only slightly lower than Xiarui's.
That means, you're only this close
to getting into Binhai Business School.
How did you know my exam results?
Aren't our results on the ChengHua Board?
I just simply took a look.
Just good memory.
Then, do you want me
to go to Binhai Business School?
Well how about you? Do you want to go?
I'm lying if I say I don't want to.
Also when I was working at Yami,
most of the customers over
there are university students.
I was quite envious when
I heard them talking about the school.
It is the taste of failing. So painful.
I don't want to experience it again.
Actually you have many strengths.
You just didn't realize it yourself.
You are meticulous, patient,
quick minded as well.
So if you want to do it,
it can be done.
Are those words really describing me?
From other people's mouth,
I'm a bad student.
Love to fight. Grumpy.
Explosive.
That's not explosive.
That's righteousness.
You are sentimental.
So you think I can?
Yes, I think you can.
We're here.
Thank you for sending me home today.
-Bye.
-Hey, Yufei.
Thank you.
No one has ever said those things to me.
Thanks for what? I should be thanking you.
Thanks for rescuing me today.
I hope I can see you at
Binhai University in the coming year.
That's a promise.
Promise.
Bye.
I heard the latest news.
The designing contest.
The great Nanxi has also participated.
I've already heard about it.
Then the game will be interesting.
At that time, I'll do
a comprehensive in-depth report.
Especially with the first-hand
information of the great Nanxi.
This time I want to dominate
the gossip forum of the school papers.
Uhh, let me interview you.
Do you have confidence going
against Nanxi in this competition?
- Nothing to do with you.
- How can this have nothing to do with me?
That Nanxi and you are a big deal!
That's the architecture school
battle between the top two.
Besides, isn't it also an
internal friendly match between dormmates?
Anyhow, I can't say it has
nothing to do with you, right?
But this time it's not
necessarily predictable.
Yesterday Nanxi was still chasing
the deadline for registration.
Now the public display of work
is only less than a month.
I'm really worried for Nanxi.
Do not worry. The great Nanxi
wouldn't sign up if he wasn't confident.
That's true.
Nanxi, Control your dormmates.
Don't let them bother me.
Since the independent students' enrolment,
you have always been number one.
This competition, I will definitely win.
Goodluck.
A true God.
That boldness, that steadiness.
Are you always that arrogant?
Not seeing anyone else but you?
No.
Or, although you are always number one
you don't care about the result at all.
This time, I care.
Then, why are you cheering for me?
Just being polite.
How about we leave now?
Feels like blood will be spilt any time.
Okay.
Hope we can do our best this time.
Your time is running out. Good luck.
I will.
Nanxi, how's the search for the wood?
It's not going well?
Would you like to talk to me about it?
First impression?
- That's the theme of this
year's competition?
- Yes.
But what's most beautiful in life
isn't the first impression.
It's our understanding
and tolerance together.
But these two pieces of wood
don't seem to be perfect.
Is it intentional?
Yes,
just as imperfect as we are.
Us.
Us?
When we are together,
we're perfect.
So you mean,
the most beautiful thing in life
isn't the first impression's rush.
But the romance in
getting to know each other?
Two pieces of basswood
shouldn't be together at all.
But they tried their best to be together.
Living the most beautiful life.
Just like us.
Right?
That's right.
So the most important thing is to
find the two suitable pieces of wood.
I'll go look with you tomorrow, okay?
We will definitely find them.
Miss, you came to the right shop.
In all of Binhai, there's nothing
you can't find at our shop.
Look at the craftwork of this wood.
As you can see, so much wood.
Look around.
Which one is more suitable for you?
Then we can both suggest our offers.
- All around, good business.
- Sure, just a moment.
What do you think?
Anything you like?
Boss, How about this?
We'll think about it back home and
contact you if we need anything.
Well, I've been serving you
for a long time taking you around.
I'm thirsty, losing my voice here!
Very sorry. It's just that
we have to think about it, isn't it?
We'll go back and think.
We'll call you if we need anything, okay?
Thank you, thank you.
- I can give a discount! I ca--
- Thank you, thank you.
These kids.
Those more realistic wood that you want,
should be here. Take a look.
Should be able to find it, right?
I'll help you look.
What are you doing?
Let me climb.
Which one do you want?
Be careful.
You be careful.
Pass me the knife.
Let me help you up there.
Don't climb too high.
Be careful.
Somebody's coming.
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- Come down! Quick!
Stop!
- Are you two really students?
- We are really students.
We just came to find the
things for him to make.
The kind of wood to participate in
a competition. Nothing else.
I've watched the surveillance video.
You didn't really do anything.
But the trees here are only for viewing.
Without governmental approval,
it's impossible to use.
Not even cutting, or selling.
Why don't you go somewhere else
to find what you want?
Stop having this idea again, okay?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Unbelievable.
Where do we go next?
I know who to look for.
In Binhai, there's nowhere that
your Uncle Wang can't look for.
Let's go!
Uncle Wang, what is this place?
Don't underestimate this place.
It's the biggest root carving
market in Binhai.
If you need wood
most of them are here.
Nanxi, do you think this is the place?
Let's see. Look for it slowly.
Since you're here,
just go with your heart.
Here, there's nothing that you can't look
for, only the unimaginable.
Thank you, Uncle Wang.
It's too much trouble for you.
Just a small matter.
Since President Ren arranged this, I will
do my best to help you find what you want.
How about this?
- Nanxi what do you think?
- This wood is so big!
Still not very satisfied.
Not yet?
What kind of wood is this?
Be careful.
This is it.
These two?
These two pieces of rotten wood?
The reason why these
two pieces of wood were abandoned,
it's because they have irregular shapes.
But in fact they came from the same tree.
Same tree.
What kind of tree is this?
It's a tree connected by root.
This piece is the south part.
This piece is the east.
All deviated from the main root.
Same
but different.
But is this in line with our theme?
You can even see that?
This son of President Ren,
is really remarkable.
Uncle Wang, I want to ask.
Is the wood for sale?
Of course. Besides,
these are all rotten wood.
Better than giving it out for free.
You just settle it here.
Stay here.
I'll go talk to them.
Okay, thank you Uncle Wang.
You're welcome.
Nanxi.
How long do you think these
two pieces of wood have been together?
About 10 years or so.
Then how long do you think they
were together when they were still trees?
About 360 years.
Just 360 years?
But I
want to be with you forever.
I want to be with you forever too.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by Nice To Meet You Team@ Viki.com
♫ The sound of the school's release bell is always so wonderful ♫
♫ The story will be the same tomorrow ♫
♫ You wear your earbuds ♫
♫ I push the bicycle to wait for you ♫
♫ No need to use language, we still feel the warmth ♫
♫ Waiting for the next vacation ♫
♫ Waiting for the next trip ♫
♫ Waiting for the next crossroad where I will present you a letter ♫
♫ The summer after graduation ♫
♫ Inside the tree hole next to the sports field ♫
♫ Store the memories I have of you ♫
♫ You are the most beautiful scenery of my memory ♫
♫ Cicadas sleep on the desks ♫
♫ The textbooks are imprinted on my face ♫
♫ The teacher's chalk ♫
♫ I am being punished to stand against the wall ♫
♫ Your eyes watch me, secretly laughing ♫
♫ The sound of the school's release bell is always so wonderful ♫
♫ The story will be the same tomorrow ♫
♫ You wear your earbuds ♫
♫ I push the bicycle to wait for you ♫
♫ No need to use language, we still feel the warmth ♫
♫ Waiting for the next vacation ♫
♫ Waiting for the next trip ♫
♫ Waiting for the next crossroad where I will present you a letter ♫
♫ The summer after graduation ♫
♫ Inside the tree hole next to the sports field ♫
♫ Store the memories I have of you ♫
♫ You are the most beautiful scenery of my memory ♫