My girl friend is an Alien
- Episode 01 -
Recenly, the Pan-STARRS 1 telescope in Hawaii
spotted an unknown spacecraft
when looking for near-earth objects for NASA.
It has been substantiated that
this unique object zooming through our solar system
is the first interstellar asteriod.
Mr. Fang,
Maybe there will be a heavy rain tonight
You should come back as soon as possible.
Got it.
Scientists suspected that
this unidentified flying object may be coming from
an extrasolar double star system.
According to the research done by Evan Jackson
and other planetary scientists of the University of Toronto...
Earthling...
This hormone smells so great.
Be mindful with your hands.
Mr. Fang,
I am here to exam you.
Since your car accident from a week ago,
we have done all the exams we can think of.
We couldn't find anything wrong with you.
Didn't you mention a shadow found in chest area?
Were you able to confirm?
Nothing abnormal was found for now.
We suspect that it is hematocele.
Mr. Fang,
Do you remember what happened?
Besides passing out due to the crash,
Nothing.
Nothing at all?
Was it raining?
Yes,
It was raining.
I see.
You can leave now.
If anything happens I will let you know.
Okay then. Take a rest, Mr. Fang.
= Wang Jianguo
Planet: Earth
Nationality: China
Initiating Program in Chinese =
Hello, Uncle Wang Jianguo.
I got lost on earth.
Now I am suppressed by gravity,
There is no way for me to go into the space.
Is this the northern hemisphere?
Help!
Well, the Earthlings are not hospitable at all.
What the heck?
Don't drop me. Don't drop me, Xiaoqi.
It's me,
your private secretary Cubrile.
Xiaobu,
what happened to you?
It was  your rescue of the male Earthling,
that I fell into the river with you.
Now my central processing unit was eaten by this tortoise.
I will have to communicate with you through this tortoise.
The transmitted sound was through low frequency sound wave.
Only you can hear me.
You have been laying in the river for seven solar days.
The spacecraft has gone on the homeward voyage.
We are so falling behind.
It is okay.
I will connect with the headquarter through my annunciator.
Where is my annunciator?
I am screwed.
I lost my annunciator.
I might have lost it on
the man I saved.
Do you remember
The face of the man you saved?
Not so much about the face.
But I do remember his
body shape.
Dear Master,
it is a sunny day today.
The temperature is about 30℃,
with humidity of 40%.
Cold air or rainfall
are not expected for the week.
Dressing index...
Mr. Fang,
Grade Four.
we got real trouble in the company.
Speak.
You ex-girl friends have rallied
in front of the company for payback.
Ex-girl friend?
Ex-girl friends.
I have made enquiries of several people.
This is a well-organized event
forcing you into marriage.
The girl friends you have abandoned...
I meant...
broke up peacefully...
have called many media
to host a live press conference in our company.
In short,
please do not come to the company today.
You just had a car accident.
I will ask for enhanced security.
I will be right there.
Mr. Fang, Mr. Fang.
We have a very enthusiastic scene here today.
I bet the brides are equally excited.
For those who are still hanging there in front of the live cam,
our main cast today
Fang leng,the eldest son of the billionaire Fang Shida,
has finally arrived.
Photographer
hurry, turn your lens towards Mr. Fang.
Mr. Fang,
what do you think of today's forcing marriage event?
Thanks for all the attention from the media.
It is a shame to cash on love
in the world.
Afterall,  love is a matter of two people.
Bring me the brides.
Mr. Fang,
Relax.
I will make them disassociate from me.
Mr. Fang,
Ever since we had dinner together,
you act as if you do not remember me.
Sunny,
No time today.
From now on,
you only need to listen to what we have to say to you.
Sunny,
your real name is Sun Yanli.
a domestic emerging fashion model.
You met with Mr. Fang on a Charity Gala last year.
How did you gather all these information?
Our F Group owns
top-notch domestic network companies.
Everything we want to know,
we do know.
This flight ticket
will send you directly to Paris
for a New Product Lauch shooting for the VOGUE Magazine.
Whether or not you can become a top model globally
depends on whether or not you seize on this opportunity.
You should know what I meant.
I understand.
Thank you very much, Mr. Fang.
Sorry for all the trouble.
Next.
See what that jackass junior
has done to our company.
May I ask the brides
your opinions on Mr. Fang being such a womanizer?
Do you have anything more to disclose?
Who said that Mr. Fang is a womanizer?
Mr. Fang was right.
Love is a matter of two people only.
It is not  proper to cash it
I hope the media
can respect our personal privacy.
What happened?
I don't know... what the heck?
Let's go. Thank you everyone.
Don't leave.
Any brides left?
That's all.
Mr. Fang,
this is the data we have compiled.
Your female-targeting amnesia
synchronizes with thunderstorm almost exactly.
Mr. Fang,
should we look for new girl friends for you?
No need.
Contact Dr. Zhang for me.
Got it.
Oh Well
Do you have the findings
for the car accident?
You were the only one on the scene,
so there was no collateral damage.
However,
there is one thing for you to have a look.
When you were in the coma,
you were holding this blue stone in your hand.
I thought it must be important to you,
so I collected it for you.
Do you have any impressions with it?
It is not mine.
Bring it to the Research Department
and ask them to find out the origin of this stone.
Got it.
Xiaoqi,
your mistake was that you couldn't resist
the temptation of the six packs of the male earthlings.
You left the spaceship recklessly to save him
knowing that lust is a deadly sin.
You made me sin with you.
Alright.
I am trying to fix it here.
You should think carefully.
And seriously.
The details, right, the details.
You should draw everything
you could remember about the earthling.
Draw it out meticulously.
It is done.
How is it?
Hold me up?
What do you mean?
Hold me up so that I can take a look.
I am a tortoise now.
Oh right.
I forgot.
See.
How is it?
How are you possibly gonna find him
with a drawing like this?
I didn't take a good look at his face.
Isn't it just about finding a man?
There is a lack of everything here on earth
except for men with two legs.
Let's go.
According to my scan of the earthlings,
there is one place we should go first.
Wow this set of clothes is really pretty.
Do I look like an earthling?
According to the ''Earth Survival Handbook''
we should resist inferior culture of the earth
corroding us Cape Townian.
Not only didn't you reject them,
you are wearing them.
I am only pretending to be an earling,
so that I can find my annunciator.
I have decided,
I am gonna wear this set.
No.
According to the handbook, on the earth
you should only wear this dress when getting married.
What is getting married?
A synonym for copulation.
Earthlings are still using primary way to breed.
It is unlike us.
We can simply login on Gene-sharing System.
I am fine with getting married with someone
if I can go out wearing such a pretty dress.
I am gonna wear this dress.
No you cannot. You cannot wear this.
Am I pretty? Am I pretty?
A thief!
Catch the thief.
Who is the thief?
It is you.
The earth has not yet evolved to a sharing society.
The trade of goods is through exchange of money.
It is an emergency.
Teleport out.
I...
You, the thief, stop right there.
Freeze.
Stop running.
The cars...
are gonna
explode.
Freeze.
Stop running.
Catch her. She is a thief.
See you.
Stop running.
Stop right there.
Generally speaking,
family of origin can affect a person's entire life,
especially  gender relations.
Your situation is more complex.
You mother died in a rainstorm.
This event
affects you deeply
on a subconscious level.
To protect yourself,
you forget the females you have met with recently
every time you experience a rainstorm.
Call it female-targeting amnesia or
neurosis self preservation.
After all,
it was because that you cannot overcome the psychological trauma.
Besides amnesia,
am I gonna hallucinate?
Freeze time
For example...
Clinically, we have never seen
anything like that.
Would it be possible that
you are experiencing too much pressure from work?
Thanks to you,
I had to dealt with dozens of brides today.
I am not the one to blame here.
Back when we were in school,
you purposefully hid your condition.
All these years I have never regretted for hidding it.
Sure. Sure.
Mr. Fang is a master strategic planner.
You have endured great hardship
and became the chief executive of the F Group
under the nose of your stepmother's.
However,
the pressing matter of the moment is that
you need to fix your problem.
You must not let them get it to you.
Good for you know.
Prescribe me some meds.
Stop the shenanigans.
Shop Opening Party.
Take you to the tropical desert.
Six-pack abs.
Xiaoqi,
didn't we make a deal that we are gonna find that earthling?
I am right here looking.
Hey.
Xiaoqi, wake up.
Do you smell anything?
Smell of what?
Hormone.
Back then, that man
lured me off the spaceship to save him
by using this smell.
Did you know?
male hormone.
Male hormone is hallucinogenic drug with Level 10 alert
on our Planet Cape Town.
It is a banned substance, Xiaoqi.
I had no choice.
Not you.
Not you neither.
None of you are the man I was looking for.
Here.
Drink this cup.
And we will be him.
Really?
Drink this cup.
And we will be him.
Cheers.
Xiaoqi.
Xiaoqi,
''Earth Survival Handbook'' has stressed that
alcohol is hallucinogenic drug.
Stay away from it.
What should I do now?
I've already drunk it.
I am not only a bit dizzy,
but also a bit excited.
You are bringing a little tortoise with you.
How adorable.
Let us take a look.
Xiaobu.
Who did this?
Who?
You... you pay for it.
You... you all...
Don't go.
Xiaobu,
is he the one I have saved?
I still remember...
A princess.
# I still remember that year #
# seeing you holding his hand. #
# But I forgot to identify #
# as a bystander.#
# Being alone and craving for the moment #
# to be hit by the memories. #
# My soul is turning to steel #
# longing for the disappearing #
# disappearing... #
Bro,
I... I am drawing pictures in the art room.
My main task today is to
combine the styles of
impressionism and brutalism.
I feel like  hearing music.
Nope.
I am just having some light music for inspiration.
Bro, no need to come to see me.
I am gonna go to bed soon.
See you tomorrow, bro.
Stop knocking. I am coming out.
Han... Bro Han...
Sorry about that, Miss.
Can you please pay the bill first?
The total is
48,965 RMB.
Please pay the bill.
What does it mean?
You ordered two bottles of red wine, worth 15,000 RMB each.
And there is more.
The male models I have hired, you picked them all.
Totaling 48,965 RMB.
Can you please pick up the check?
I don't have any money.
Whose daughter is this?
Jack Ma has one son that I can recall of.
and Sephirex Wang doesn't have any sisters neither.
An illegitimate child?
Whatever. None of my business.
She spends money like water.
She must come  from a rich family.
Miss.
You are awake.
I have prepared breakfast for you.
You must be hungry.
Who are you?
Where is it?
I am the boss lady of this place.
You can call me Ms. Chai.
Don't you remember?
Last night
you were partying with us.
You had a great time.
It got too late.
I was afraid it would be dangerous for you to go out alone
so I took you in.
Thank you,
Earthling.
Earthling?
Didn't expect you to be a funny gal.
Miss,
you are probably a Rich White Beauty, right?
What is a Rich White Beauty?
Don't be so modest.
You are dressed up like a little princess.
You must be coming from a wealthy family.
I don't have parents.
Ah?
So you are an orphan...
I am not an orphan.
The children on our planet
are bred through gene pool.
We have been long evolved away from the
low-level sexual reproduction method of the earth.
Is this girl out of her mind?
I would be damned.
That's not important.
Just tell me,
what is your name,
and where is your home.
My name is Gillis Cal Qiuso Cara Cara Number Seven.
Are you kidding me?!
Is it because the name a bit long?
I go by Xiaoqi.
Thank you Earthling.
I have to go now. I have something important to do.
Stop right there.
You spent money, do you understand?
Ah?
You spent money here in my shop last night.
You pick a bunch of male models.
Did you forget?
You touched them all.
Here is the tab
plus accommodation,
Water, electricity, and cleaning...
200,000 RMB minimum.
I will give you 20% off.
Let's say 120,000 RMB.
Pay it now.
I don't have money.
What?
You don't have any money?
Who are you kidding?!
You are dressed like a million dollars,
wearing such expensive watch.
And you claim you have no money?
You like this watch?
Here you are.
This watch
is not enough of payment.
Go on.
Oh my goodness.
Why am I falling on evil days?
I hosted such a big party.
Who was it for?
Was it for myself?
I was for every one.
Yet you played with the models, had a great time,
drank the wine,
and I paid my vendors,
you bill on me.
Why? Who was it for?
I don't wanna live anymore.
According to the handbook,
the tears of earthlings represent sadness.
Ms. Chai,
Ms. Chai, do not cry, no more.
You wanna me to pay the bill, right?
I will do anything for you
if you stop crying.
I promise.
Okay.
Done.
How is it?
Have you memorized the Code of Conduct of the deliveryman?
Don't worry.
I have great memory.
In your words,
a photographic memory.
Your confused
little brain.
You cannot even remember your name.
Of course I can.
My name is Gillis Cal Qiuso Cara Cara Number Seven.
Stop, stop.
I beg you, from now on
please do not introduce yourself like that.
People would think you are a psycho.
How about this.
What are the odds that we ran into each other.
You can take my surname.
My surname is Chai.
So you will be Chai Xiaoqi.
Chai Xiaoqi.
A beautiful name.
Though we have a bond,
business is business.
Don't worry.
as long as I have a bite-size food,
you will not be the one to starve.
There are good people on the earth.
SugarBomb rejected.
Get to work.
See you later.
Mr. Fang.
Xiaolie has agreed to isolate himself for creation.
Are we gonna interrupt him
barging into his studio?
Exhibition is about to be open to the public.
We cannot indulge his procrastination any longer.
Have you sent help to lock him up?
Of course.
I can promise not even a fly can come out of that place.
Cars.
Mr. Han,
did you see a person standing right there?
Nope.
You cannot come in now.
That is unacceptable.
My boss lady has requested
that we must  deliver personally to the client.
And I cannot leave without a five-star rating.
I said no.
What's all the fuss about?
My boss lady...
The prince.
Are you seriously questioning the deliveryman?
Am I a prisoner?
I am gonna complain to Mr. Fang
that you guys abuse artist.
See,
you are bullying a little girl.
Come in quick.
Let me see if they had hurt you.
You look even better in the daylight
compared to moonlight.
Moonlight?
You saw my show last night?
Yes.
It was rare chance that I got on stage.
It is fate brought us together.
Eh!
My name is Fang Lie.
My name is Gillis Cal...
My name is Xiaoqi.
We are friends now.
Your business is my business.
And my business is your business.
So take off your clothes.
Ah?
Take... take my clothes off?
As you can see,
I am held here against my will.
And you are the only one who can help me to escape.
Escape?
That is...
let me change into your clothes
and get out.
But why are they holding you?
Are you a villain?
Of course not. I am not a villain.
An unscrupulous businessman held me here to paint paintings.
He thought artwork is no different from water from faucet.
You can just turn it on, and artwork flows out.
Art is an explosion of emotion,
a thrill of inspiration.
It is above this world.
How come you are so good-looking even when you are reasoning?
Let it out.
How can I help you?
It is really simple. I will wear your clothes and walk out the door.
And you will
pretend to be me and stay here.
Don't worry.
That businessman will only be hard on me.
You will not be implicated.
Sounds good.
Mr. Fang,
the exhibition starts next month.
you can take a vacation
once you have prepared all the artworks.
Have I seen you before?
Don't get close to me.
I don't know any bad guys like you.
Keeping an artist in captivity illegally.
Where is Fang Lie?
I am not gonna say a word.
Stay away from me.
Stay away from me. If you come any closer,
I am gonna scare you to death using my power.
This is strange... why isn't anything happening?
Don't do anything stupid.
I am not gonna make it difficult for you.
All you need to do is telling me where did Fang Lie go?
Mr. Fang,
what happened?
Who is this?
Mr. Fang, be careful.
No need to chase her.
She can run, but she cannot hide.
Find her,
and you will be able to find Fang Lie.
Ms. Chai.
Ms. Chai,
I am sorry.
I lost my work clothes.
How did it get back?
A handsome boy just dropped it off.
He was here.
He really came back for me.
Oh right,
he left you a business card here for you.
He said tonight,
he will wait for you in the restaurant on the top floor.
Xiaoqi, I mean...
this is just your first day,
how come you are hooking up with client ?
I...
I am...
I mean it as a compliment.
I am in need of staff like you
who can quickly become friends with clients.
Do you understand?
Ms. Chai, how many deliveries are still out?
I will try to finish them early so that I can take off.
You can still make delivery?
Of course.
I'm full of strength now.
Xiaoqi,
you are a man in short supply.
I will go upstairs.
Ms. Chai, I am back.
Ms. Chai?
Stop yelling.
I booked the whole floor.
I am the only one you need to serve.
Chai Xiaoqi, Chai Xiaoqi.
Our biggest client has personally requested for you to stay
How can you say no?
Get back in.
But Ms. Chai,
haven't I clocked out already?
What do you mean?
You don't want to work overtime?
How can you be so selfish?
Can you please think for others?
Can you think for me?
Can you think for this shop?
Do you really have to see that...
Overtime.
Sure I can do overtime.
I can.
I am okay with overtime.
Overtime makes me happy.
Overtime is fulfilling.
I love overtime.
Yeah.
Dear customer,
all the dishes are on the menu.
Please take a look.
No need.
Bring me everything
you delivered to the hotel today.
Kitchen crew?
They are dismissed.
How about this.
You make it yourself.
You can make one for yourself as well.
Once we are fed,
bring me to Fang Lie.
The one you aid to escape today.
I am really sorry.
Our restaurant doesn't provide outsourcing service.
In fact,
I can only make deliveries.
I cannot cook.
If you have a problem with that,
you can go and find another restaurant.
Boss lady.
I will make it.
Cooking is a piece of cake.
wait here.
I will make you a meal.
Making meal is fulfilling.
An unscrupulous businessman
just like a dead rock on Jinkela
as hard and as stinky.
Wait there, I will be right back.
What is this thing?
The things on earth are so strange.
Xiaobu, Xiaobu,
look it up quick, look it up for me.
Xiaobu,
I dropped a little wine onto you
and you cannot speak anymore?
Fine, I will figure it out myself.
And then add this.
Add...
What is happening?
What are you doing?
I am cooking.
Bring me a fire extinguisher.
What does a fire extinguisher look like?
Are you a pig?
I...
So you are the person I was trying to find.
What are you saying?
Stay there.
Please.
Your hormones is too aggressive .
I feels like freezing.
Can you speak human language?