I'm self-willed and act like a baby to make you angry,
but you always stay so calm.
Until you are beaten by my loveliness,
I will consider leaving the solar system.
The universe has gravitation, has gravitation,
and you have a fatal attraction to me.
Even the path of half of the universe
can't stop me.
I have the sadness of being homeless,
while you have the warmth like the sun.
I've been through tens of millions of light-years
just to be loved by you.
I am the love of the moon following the planet.
You are the charming danger of flying over the asteroid belt.
I've wandered for tens of millions of light-years
just to be found by you and to be remembered forever.
My Girlfriend is an Alien
Episode 24
The time limit of one week is about to expire.
You didn't come to me after so long a time.
Do you really want to resign?
You got it wrong.
This is my own problem.
I will solve it by myself.
Saying this,
you must have figured out a way,
Not yet.
But I have come up with some thoughts.
If things can progress quickly...
So you don't have a solution.
Fang Leng,
get married with Jiang Xue, will you?
Under the current circumstances,
with our own strength,
we can't reverse the situation.
Only when we form an alliance with Xue,
can we secure your position.
I know the people in the company very well.
In all the past years,
though they haven't said anything,
they
have had issues with your holding the post
of President of the company at such a young age.
Now,
it is so lucky for them to have this chance.
They will definitely figure out a way to kick you out.
Therefore,
only Xue
can pull you out of the mire.
If I want to remain in the mire, what will you do?
Dad,
till now, you haven't got it clear
why I have got into such a plight.
It is not because my illness was exposed,
and not because the others objected to me,
but because I am a sick person for real
and something is wrong with me.
It is normal for me to be questioned by the others.
However, I want to stay to prove myself.
I want to prove that
a sick person
can also manage a company well.
This is the right way, isn't it?
In my opinion, your thoughts
are too naive.
My amnesia
is like a blemish of me.
I have been concealing it
all the time.
But finally it was found out.
When everyone waited to see
how I would cover up
this problem of me,
there was only one person
who said that everyone would lose memories,
and I only lost more memories than the others.
On that day,
I began to feel
that it is not a blemish at all.
You don't want to marry Jiang Xue
not only because you want to prove yourself, right?
There is another reason known to you.
I love another girl...
Enough!
It is OK that you don't love Jiang Xue.
But you can't
put our family behind yourself.
So do you mean that
you want me to
make a choice between our Fang family and Xiaoqi?
Fang Leng,
you can take it that I, as your dad,
am begging you.
Mom.
What are you doing?
You scared me.
Why did come you back so early?
Because I missed you
and couldn't concentrate on work.
Where is dad?
He is having a talk with Fang Leng inside.
What is the talk about?
Let's go talk in your room.
Go! Go! Go!
Well, what is the matter?
Let's go.
What?
All people have their own fates.
Fang Leng just abandons the broad road
and chooses to walk on the one-plank bridge
with Chai Xiaoqi.
This isn't good.
I have to persuade my dad.
You can do nothing about it.
Even if we join hands,
we are no better than Fang Leng.
Even Fang Leng can do nothing about it.
What can you do?
What if Leng insists in not marrying Jiang Xue
and is beside himself with rage.
Then it will suit him well.
I didn't mean that.
I mean that he will get what he wants.
It is fine as long as Fang Leng think it is OK.
You want to put in a word.
How can you do that?
You want to make Chai Xiaoqi
daughter-in-law of our family.
But could that be possible?
Why isn't it possible?
As long as she is not married with Leng,
it will be fine.
What did you say?
Nothing, mom.
Please leave.
I am perturbed in mind.
Didn't you say you missed me?
I will stay with you a little longer.
Please leave now.
Why?
You are back.
Hmm.
I have sorted out all materials.
Have a look!
I also prepared
questionnaires about the perfume preferences.
Tomorrow we can conduct relevant research together.
What is wrong with you?
Were you scolded by your dad?
No, I wasn't.
My dad was worried about me.
So he called me over to have a talk.
That's quite good.
Xiaoqi.
Mm.
About this project,
I still have a lot of things to think about.
You may leave first.
Aren't you in a hurry?
It doesn't matter.
I can accompany you to work overtime.
You need not.
You.
You have done a lot for me.
For the next.
it is time for me to make a good choice.
Just go back.
Just go.
Then I am off.
Good night!
Assistant Han.
Why are you here?
Xiaoqi,
let's elope, shall we?
Are you crazy?
Why shall we elope?
It makes no sense.
Don't you want to help Leng?
What do you mean?
My dad
wants me to take the place of Leng.
If I leave,
my dad will be left with no choice.
He can only turn to Leng.
Thus, if we elope,
it will be of great help for him.
Oh.
Do you mean that
you want to help Fang Leng very much?
Yes.
For you,
is the brotherhood between you and your Leng
really very important?
Of course.
Hmm.
Then you can leave alone.
Why do you get me involved?
Because in my heart, you are more important than him.
As long as you are with me,
I can give up everything.
Whether it is the family
or work,
I can abandon them all.
But if you are together with Leng...
What if I am together with your Leng?
Mr. Fang.
From now on,
all work in the charge of me shall be suspended.
Why?
Isn't there
any other solution to address the crisis?
You won't be together with him.
Even if you want to be together with him,
he won't choose you.
Why?
Because he is different from me.
I can be childish.
I can be wayward.
But he can't.
He can give up his career for you,
but he can never abandon our Fang family and dad for you.
Therefore, Xiaoqi,
please agree to
leave with me.
As long as we leave,
Leng won't have a hard time making choices.
What did you say?
If I stay here,
Fang Leng won't be able to deal with the crisis?
As long as I give up on Xiaoqi,
I can resolve all crises.
Anyway,
time is running out.
You only need to leave with me.
We can come back later if you want.
OK.
I believe you.
No matter what the reason is,
even if my departure can help Fang Leng,
I won't leave him.
But I won't give up.
You are Fang Leng's younger brother.
Why don't you know him?
You have followed me for a long time.
You should know me well.
In my eyes,
Fang Leng is calm
and strong.
Even if he is thrown down into the dirt by others,
he would stand up again.
Since childhood,
I have never admitted defeat to anyone.
When he gets into trouble,
he will never resort to others for help.
Because it is harder for him
to do that than to fail.
If I have to betray my feelings to keep my career,
that will be a greater humiliation for me than failure.
Therefore,
I won't sacrifice myself
to help him secure his career.
Therefore, I won't sacrifice Xiaoqi
in exchange for the success of my career.
You said you would work for me.
Why are you standing here on the curbside?
Why are you here?
I have solved all problems.
For the next, of course I will come to you.
Why do you
come to me?
Of course, I have come to you for your help.
Let's go.
Wait a moment.
As you said,
you have conducted the survey for me.
Don't laugh at me.
I know that
the project survey
should be conducted at the very beginning.
It is of use for me to do anything now.
If I really do nothing,
there will be no hope at all.
Who said it would of no use?
These answers
may give us a lot of inspirations.
Let me have a look.
=Questionnaire about the Perfume Preference=
Stop flipping it.
Standing there for a long time,
I only completed a few questionnaires.
It doesn't matter.
These questionnaires may provide the best answers
even if there are only a few of them.
The answers in all of them are the same.
Speaking of perfume,
they just want to use it to attract the persons they love.
We'd better read the previous materials.
We may find some good ideas.
Wait a minute.
If all the answers are the same...
You said that they use perfume to
to attract the others, right?
Yes.
The perfume is just like the hormone of humans.
Hormone?
Yes.
When I just arrived here,
I couldn't resist the hormone
given off by men at all.
As long as I pick up the scent,
within three minutes,
I will be like a drunken person.
Right.
Three minutes!
Within three minutes,
one person will be made intoxicated
and fall in love with the other person.
Three minutes later,
when the smell of the perfume fades away,
the person will regain sanity.
However, the other person got a chance because of this.
It is a chance of falling in love.
Don't you think this is an excellent scheme?
Oh.
Of course.
But it is impossible for our company
to create such wonderful perfume.
Who said that?
It is a piece of cake for me.
Let's get started?
Where should we start?
Xiaoqi.
Get your things
and go sleep in the bedroom.
Have you done all your work?
How about you?
These are the ingredients I preliminarily prepared.
However, I haven't
asked the lab personnel to test them.
So the effects are still unknown.
It only took a week to do this.
It can be said to be a miracle.
I will go to the company with the scheme first.
After I convince them,
we will go on with the next step in the lab.
Hmm.
Xiaoqi,
when I release the news,
I hope you can be present.
After all, you helped me
finish this scheme.
No matter how things turn out,
I hope you can be by my side.
I mean,
in the event that we can't convince them,
what should we do?
Then I will live off you.
Get prepared
to be responsible for me.
You bad guy!
Then I will go back to the restaurant now.
I will straighten out things.
I will go to join you in the company after I am done.
OK!
Naughty!
Miss Chai,
it has been a long time.
It is you!
What do you want?
Don't get nervous.
To meet you,
I have waited here for the whole night.
I have nothing to say with you.
Don't you fear
I will disclose your secret
and let Mr. Fang know you are a monster?
What did you say?
I didn't follow you.
Actually,
I don't want to give you a hard time.
As long as you tell me your identity,
I promise
no one will know your secret.
How about you?
What is your purpose?
So you really don't know?
Why is Fang Leng here?
Where is your wound?
Don't touch me!
Get your hands off me! Don't touch me!
Where is your wound?
Let go of me!
You!
What is the matter with you?
You are right.
I am a monster indeed.
If you dare to threaten me again,
I can kill you now.
Do you think I am afraid of you?
Why are you here?
If my memory didn't lie to me,
today is supposed to
the day when you hold the lunch press conference?
How you figured out what to do?
Of course.
Thank you for your care, Miss Jiang!
Wait up!
Uncle Fang should have told you, didn't he?
I want to help you sincerely.
If you are talking about our marriage,
I can give you my answer now.
Jiang Xue,
please stop selling yourself as goods.
You have gone so far.
You have made all efforts.
Instead of me,
the person you should care about
is yourself.
What do you mean?
Look at you!
You are smart,
and independent.
You have your own career.
The most important thing for you now
is to find a person
who loves you wholeheartedly.
Isn't this what you really want?
Don't have your hands tied with me?
Let go of me.
Then you can walk out of the dilemma for real.
I believe in the days to come,
you will find real happiness.
Thank you for loving me once.
The managerial personnel and journalists are all here.
OK.
Mr. Fang will arrive in a moment.
Mr. Fang.
Has Xiaoqi arrived?
Isn't she with you?
Call her.
Nobody answered the phone.
Might anything have happened to her?
The launch press conference is about to start right away.
Send someone to go to the restaurant to pick her up.
Ask her to come in a hurry.
Yes.
Where is this place?
You came round?
Come on.
Let me untie you.
Sorry.
I cut the wrong place.
However,
this is not supposed to be the blood of the earthlings.
Could I saw wrongly again?
You have discovered this last time,
haven't you?
Say it.
Who are you on earth?
If I tell you,
will you let me go?
That's the condition I proposed last time.
It is a different case now.
Whether I will let you go or not
depends on my mood.
You!
Miss Chai,
you are in my hands now.
Even if you don't tell me,
I will find it out with my ability.
Nonetheless,
you are such a great
experimental article.
It will be a great waste if I don't experiment on you.
Ah.
You must hurry.
What do you mean?
Haven't you found that
my body temperature has begun to fall?
If you don't hurry up,
I may die.
By then,
your experimental article will be useless for sure.
You lied to me.
I just cut you lightly once.
Why will you die?
It has nothing to do with your cut.
It is because you touched my hand.
My skin
can't come into direct contact with the earthling.
You said I am an earthling.
So you are
really an alien?
Why need I joke with you
at the cost of my life?
If you want to save my life,
you should hurry to warm me up.
I won't be taken in by you.
You want to send me away.
Then you can take the chance to escape, right?
If I had been able to escape,
I would have killed you.
Why should I remain here being tortured by you?
Then behave yourself!
Chai Xiaoqi!
OK!
I got it.
What is the matter?
Xiaoqi didn't go back to the restaurant at all.
Ms. Chai and Fang Lie also said they didn't see her.
It is really unknown where she has gone.
Shall I send people to look for her?
It is time for the launch press conference.
You'd better go first.
Something is wrong.
She agreed to meet me in the company today.
It is such an important conference.
It is impossible for her to stand me up.
Notify the Scientific Research Department
to locate the positioning of her mobile phone.
I must know where she is.
Hmm.
Why is Xiaoqi missing?
Miss Chai.
Chai Xiaoqi!
Chai Xiaoqi, wake up!
If you don't wake up,
I will get you wounded again.
This,
this is the sapphire.
No wonder
she tried to steal it.
I will see,
I will see what other secrets you have.
What are you doing?
Don't inject the strange liquid
into my body.
Don't be afraid.
I am
just
doing this to make you coordinate with my research.
My research.
Hmm.
Mm.
How is it?
Her positioning has been locked.
It is in a remote factory in the suburbs.
Why did she go to the factory?
The reason is unknown.
It is unclear how she is now.
We can't call the police arbitrarily.
Mr. Fang,
for the next,
what should we do?
It is impossible for her to go to such a faraway place.
Even if she goes there,
she will contact me first to let me know it.
What do you mean?
Has Xiaoqi been abducted by someone?
However,
it is really possible based on her personality.
Let's find her first.
-Leng, wait up! -Mr. Fang.
I will go find her.
You will be done if you are absent from
the launch press conference.
No, I must go.
I have a hunch that
she must have gone into trouble.
Notify everyone that the launch press conference
will be postponed.
I must find Xiaoqi first.
Mr. Fang.
I will entrust everything to you.
=Roundabout=
Leng, on the right ahead.
Turn left ahead.
We are almost there.
Xiaoqi!
Are you all right?
I can't die.
I have to see Fang Leng
make a success.
I have promised him.
I am sorry.
I will break my promise.
I am here. Don't worry.
It's all right now.
Sorry!
Really.
Fang Leng, I am sorry!
I am
sorry!
Go.
Let's go over there.
Is she there?
No.
This way.
Fang Leng.
Xiaoqi.
Xiaoqi, are you all right?
You will be all right.
I won't allow anything to happen to you.
Ever since I met you,
I've just wanted to forget all the past.
The love I want doesn't have the date of return,
only you.
We're out of reach
but appreciate each other.
I keep going and run into your track somehow.
The yearning invades
and lurks in my mind.
The more I want to escape, the more
I am pulled by it bearing pains.
I'm getting addicted to it
and my sense is shielded.
There is no trace of the reason for this moment.
Put the hottest heart
in this cold body.
I'm looking at you,
and my love has nowhere to go.
Ever since I met you,
I've just wanted to forget all the past.
Every day is a new memory
which is only be about you and me.
I can't lie to myself anymore.
Please give me the courage to believe.
The love I want doesn't have the date of return,
only you.
Even everything becomes silent,
I still have you.