My Girlfriend is an Alien
- Episode 27 -
Oh my God!
Why am I here?
Your smell...
Do you like me?
Yes.
Since when?
Since the first time I met you.
You were hurt.
So I treated you in my spaceship.
I was thinking
you'd better be single.
Then
I could take you home.
But,
if you had loved one,
I would probably be very sad.
But I'd still like you.
Very good.
What's good?
The hormone perfume is perfect for interrogation.
You're almost spilled out how old your mom is.
Is it talking?
Hah.
Yea,
It is threatening you.
Can you introduce it to me?
It's called Xiaobu,
my personal secretary
and A.I. in my home planet.
But on the earth,
it's just a normal turtle.
I'm done.
I'm exposed too.
All because of you, a nasty human!
So you will also become a normal earthling in the future?
There's no future for me.
What is wrong?
What do you mean by "no future"?
My energy is running out.
After this dance with you,
I don't know if I
could still stand tomorrow.
Is it because of the annunciator?
Now, the Three Minutes Love Ball is over.
Though the magic of love lasts for only three minutes,
a happy life shall be acquired on your own.
Come on, everyone. Let's keep the mood high.
Goodness!
What did I say?
Xiaoqi.
Should this annunciator be taken out?
No, no, no.
You can't do that.
It's too dangerous.
Dangerous?
Why do you know?
Stop questioning me.
Xiaoqi.
Never ever can you do that.
If you do that,
I'll hate you forever.
Xiaoqi.
Xiaoqi didn't go this way, did she?
We're not going for her,
but for the annunciator that can bring her home.
You've made her talk!
Oh my God.
The hormone perfume is amazing.
When people are in love,
there's full of beautiful lies
and absolute loyalty.
Take it easy.
If anything happens to us,
there will be none to help Xiaoqi find that thing.
No need for finding.
The annunciator is just in my heart.
Wait. Brother.
You can't be gonna open your chest to take it out, can you?
Brother.
Brother. You can't do that!
Brother!
Doctor.
Is it really irremovable?
No.
It has been a miracle that
the foreign matter doesn't kill you.
Taking it out by force is too risk.
Even if our best Professor Gao comes to perform the surgery,
the success rate will be lower than thirty percent.
What if I just want the thirty percent?
Brother, are you crazy?
Do you understand what thirty percent means?
You have a death wish?
Your younger brother is rather rational.
Please do persuade him.
Doctor.
Brother.
For a long time,
you're the one who do the lecture.
And I don't want to say something profound.
Just think about our dad,
and our family.
No way will I allow you to do that.
I owe my life to Xiaoqi in the first place.
I can't see Xiaoqi die, Fang Lie.
I don't want her to die either.
We can think up another way, can't we?
There's no time.
Do you know?
I saw Xiaoqi pass out.
She can barely stand up.
I won't give up this method.
Compared to having died in that car accident,
it has been worthwhile for me.
At least now,
I still have thirty percent of success rate.
I still may live again.
Isn't it Xiaoqi's pet?
What do you want?
You're trying to talk to me?
The...The turtle is intelligent!
Give me a second.
Brother.
Do you want Xiaobu to draw lots?
Can you stop making noise?
Don't scare it.
Brother.
It is not talking.
Xiaoqi maybe told a lie to you, didn't she?
Xiaobu.
Is there anything you need on the table?
If there has,
stretch your head.
If not, you can wag your tail.
Brother!
Oh my God!
It really can understand you!
Xiaobu,
how can I communicate with you?
Brother,
does it intend to type?
Oh.
= Don't move. =
Wow.
I must take a short video of this.
This is amazing!
Brother.
Ouch, ouch!
It hurts.
I've told you. Don't bother it.
OK.
Don't make noise, do you?
OK, OK, OK.
Look, Xiaobu also says it.
Don't do the surgery!
Don't do the surgery. You'll die!
It seems that our magic turtle
also has no way to deal with it.
We'd better go home and think about it calmly.
Let's go. Let's go.
I see.
I'll do the surgery right away.
Why?
Look.
Don't do the surgery.
You'll die.
Unless you take me into the operating room,
probably I can
use my planet's technology to help you.
Hoo.
Xiaoqi can only drink water now.
She has no more energy
to digest food on the earth.
Go help her.
Don't let her eat anything else.
Xiaobu.
Where have you been?
Xiaobu. Xiaobu.
Xiaobu.
Weird.
Where has it gone?
Stolen by someone?
But who could be interested in a turtle?
Oh, at his place!
Ow!
But I can't win him in a fight now.
And he has hormone perfume.
It's like walking into a trap
for me to go find him now.
Xiaoqi.
Time to eat.
You haven't eaten for long.
Listen.
A person
can lose his memory,
and lose his love,
but he can't lose his appetite.
Do you know that?
Eat now.
Ms. Chai.
I don't have no appetite now.
I've brought it up to you.
Are you expecting me to feed you?
This sound is familiar.
It must be from a nice car.
Is it that Mr. Fang come to meet you?
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Don't eat now.
Come with me.
Ms. Chai.
Where's Mr. Fang?
Why doesn't he come?
He's occupied.
He told me to bring something here.
Mr. Fang heard Xiaoqi is on a diet,
so he told me to bring some imported
nutrition drinks here.
After drinking this,
she will no longer need to have a meal.
How magical it is!
No more nutrition now.
Nutrition on the earth is hard to digest.
Drinking water is enough.
Xiaoqi.
Have a try.
Yea.
One taste may not be hurt.
This is not nutrition drink at all.
Just plain water.
Why does he suddenly
send me water?
How about it?
Delicious?
Not bad.
Really?
Let me try it too.
Sorry, Ms. Chai.
Mr. Fang
emphasized that
this is for Xiaoqi only.
No longer
should she eat anything else.
They have known something or what?
Alright.
The delivery has been done.
I gotta go.
Hold on. Hold on.
I...
Anything else, Miss Xiaoqi?
I have a pet.
That turtle I mean.
I accidentally left it in Mr. Fang's place.
Can you help me to retrieve it?
Mr. Fang is very fond of that pet lately.
After a couple of days,
Mr. Fang will bring it back to you himself.
Please be patient now.
Unreasonable.
How could he give some bottles of water
in exchange of my Xiaobu?
But how could he know I can only drink water now?
Because of Xiaobu?
But Xiaobu's talking frequency
can't be understood by earthlings.
Weird.
I've analyzed the surgery plan.
Mostly inadvisable.
I'll sign a liability waiver.
You're not concerned with any risks.
Mr. Fang.
I'm being responsible for you.
The shade on the CT
is really a fragment from the car accident.
We must be fully prepared before taking it out.
I can't wait.
If you really are unwilling to perform,
I can arrange other doctors for this.
Even I, the director of cardiology,
don't dare perform it easily,
who can be so irresponsible to perform it?
How about me?
Professor Gao.
Aren't you on a academic visit in the U.S.?
For someone's invitation,
I'm obliged.
Why do you come here?
Why can't I come?
Though I don't like you anymore,
as your friend,
I have to help you at the crucial moment.
Luckily,
I know uncle Gao who can help us.
After the success of surgery,
remember to treat me to dine.
Thank you in advance.
Mr. Fang.
Let's discuss the details of the surgery together.
OK.
Please.
Wait here.
This surgery is very dangerous.
I was thinking how to stop him.
Aren't you afraid anything would go wrong?
Of course.
After all, I used to love him.
I also want him to be safe and sound.
Then why do you...
Rest assured.
I've consulted with uncle Gao.
We won't force to take it out.
Besides, with Fang Leng's character,
his decision can't be reversed no matter what.
Determined as he is,
we should find someone worth trust.
I didn't expect you to be
so helpful at the crucial moment.
I'm quite charming when I am not
carried away by love.
= Xiaoqi =
Sorry, I have to go out.
My brother's surgery...
Rest assured.
I'll contact you if something happens.
Thanks.
Anything urgent?
Fang Lie.
Do you still take me as your friend?
Of course.
I swear I do.
Why do I feel
you've defected to your brother?
Took me to the bar out of no reason.
Well...
I didn't know he was there.
Never mind. Let's put it aside.
Have you seen my Xiaobu
around your brother?
That turtle?
Of course.
It was a killer.
Killer?
Oh.
It's cyberspeak.
It means Xiaobu is adorable.
Is he going to take my Xiaobu as hostage
and threaten me?
Of course not.
Since he remembered you,
he had come up with a big plan.
Plan for what?
I've deleted it
I never expected a returning back.
You
are only stubborn in speaking.
Wait.
Has he known I'm
an alien now?
I didn't say that.
It's the hormone perfume's fault.
God.
What on earth have I said to him?
Why do I recall nothing?
I have to see him in person.
Tell me where he is?
He...
Why are you looking away?
Seriously?
You're even going to deceive me?
You're my last good friend.
When people are in love,
there's full of beautiful lies,
and absolute loyalty.
Alright.
I won't lie.
Xiaoqi.
Doctor will play it by ear.
He won't take the annunciator forcibly.
Xiaoqi.
So my brother is right.
You're out of condition,
which makes the surgery more necessary.
Xiaobu is the one I'm worried about.
It always wanted to take the annunciator out before.
Now it offers to communicate with Fang Leng.
It must have planned it.
You mean
that turtle will harm my brother?
For saving me,
it's of high possibility that it will harm Fang Leng.
What are you two doing?
How long has he been in surgery?
How long that lasts?
Any problems here?
He's been there for quite a while.
Open up.
Open up. Open the door now!
Open up!
You've lost your mind, Xiaoqi?
Here is hospital!
Open up!
Xiaobu, don't harm Fang Leng.
Do you hear me?
Let's begin.
Xiaobu,
open the door!
Xiaoqi.
Xiaobu! Xiaobu!
Clam down.
Xiaobu.
If you can hear me,
don't be so willful, OK?
Xiaobu.
Xiaobu, please don't.
Xiaobu, please, don't be so willful,
ok?
Xiaobu, I beg you.
Open the door.
Xiaobu.
Xiaobu, please.
Open the door, Xiaobu.
You such a fool.
Just a little more to finish.
Xiaoqi.
Do you remember
the first time we arrived at the earth?
We came to this world
just to appreciate the sun on earth
and collect plants and fruits here
for our planet's species diversity.
If we got luck,
we might go to see the polar light.
Never did we expect a love story on the earth.
Look yourself now.
Crying and whining.
It'll be disgraceful if you go back home.
Do you think I'd given up like this?
No.
I must take the annunciator out
for you may go back home to disgrace yourself.
However,
I will try my best to protect him
even if sacrifice myself.
Xiaoqi, Let's go see the doctor.
Uncle Gao.
How is the surgery?
Who is Chai Xiaoqi?
I am.
This is what Mr. Fang asked me to give you.
He said you can go home now.
Go home?
This is...
Let me see him.
- I want to see him. - Xiaoqi.
Mr. Fang also said,
he didn't want to see you.
Is there anything wrong with him?
Please, doctor.
Just let me see him.
I beg you, please.
Can't you understand?
He asked you to leave.
He came to the hospital every time all because of you.
Is the slap last time
not enough to wake you up?
Take your thing and get lost now.
Jiang Xue,
don't do it too far.
My brother hasn't said anything.
Why are you so furious?
It's obvious from what he said, isn't it?
Asking her to leave.
Xiaobu.
Are you OK?
Fang Leng. He's alright.
Take it easy.
Let's go home.
Hold on!
We will go home.
You can get in now.
But,
don't make the patient emotional.
Eh.
He should be fine now.
I shall go back.
Don't you want to see my brother?
No.
I said I'd give up him.
Besides,
I'm not the one he desires to see.
Why were you so arrogant just now when knowing that?
I didn't mean to pick on Xiaoqi.
I just want Fang Leng to get well soon.
Xiaoqi is his sickness.
He won't get well as long as she is here.
Some sickness can't be cured.
Or,
you wouldn't have come to help my brother.
Aren't you the same?
Wish we both could get well soon.
Brother, feeling better?
She's left?
Yes.
Don't you know
you almost died by that turtle?
Impossible.
What's impossible?
Xiaoqi has told me already.
That turtle has been wanting you dead for a long time.
I am still live and strong, am I not?
You're really making me angry.
Doing something totally crazily.
Stupid as Xiaoqi.
I could only trust it.
Though there's some twists
I eventually won the bet.
Yes, you won.
Xiaoqi also went home.
Happy now?
We will never see her again.
Brother, are you alright?
It's OK we won't see her.
At least I know
she's still alive somewhere.
Eat it now.
Your turtle body
favors this most, doesn't it?
I've spared half of my energy to you.
It's time for you to wake up.
Or I spare you the other half once more.
No.
You're awake.
Come out. Come out.
But
you have to promise me,
if I come out
you won't hit me.
I won't.
I even want to award you.
You helped me to retrieve the annunciator,
didn't you?
Come out.
I won't hit you.
OK?
You willful
deceitful
bad turtle.
You broke your promise.
Crafty as human.
Are you not?
You deceived him into performing the surgery.
You see,
we both learn how to deceive now.
We're both stained by this earth.
Press the annunciator now.
Everything will be fine when we get home.
If I press it,
can't we
go back the earth again?
We are doomed to not belong here.
Don't you give up until our energy runs out?
But I haven't said
goodbye to him properly.
He even doesn't want to see you.
No need for goodbye now.
Just press it.
Press it.
The spaceship needs time to come here.
No.
I must see him for the last time.
Where is he?
Excuse me,
where is the patient here?
He's left.
Left?
He's alright now?
He's almost recovered.
Just few examinations need to do.
Our director tried to persuade him for several times.
But the patient insisted on leaving.
I heard his little brother say
he was trying to avoid somebody.
Avoid somebody?
When did he leave?
Just finished the procedures.
Probably still downstairs.
Fang Lie.
Open the door for me.
Fang Leng. Fang Lie.
- Open the door. Fang Lie. - Let's go.
Fang Lie.
Brother.
Fang Leng. Wait please.
Fang Lie.
Go.
Fang Lie, open the door.
Fang Lie.
Don't start the car.
Fang Lie! Fang Lie! Fang Leng!
Fang Lie.
Don't leave.
We treat her like this...
Isn't it a bit cruel?
If I remember correctly,
such speed can't get rid of her.
She can pause the time,
and even get into our car by light speed.
But look at her now.
She is not the Chai Xiaoqi she used to be.
I think
Xiaoqi is kinda miserable.
She can stop being like this
as long as she goes back.
She is concerned about you.
One of us has to
give up first.
Just let her hate me.
Brother.
Should I pick this or not?
Why not pick the phone?
What can you say to her?
You thought not picking
will solve the problem?
Brother,
Xiaoqi seems really pissed off by you.
Fang Leng.
At six p.m.,
I'll wait for you on the Renmin Bridge.
If you don't come,
I'll throw the annunciator into the river.
I mean it.
Hey.
Just reply her, can you?
If she really throws it,
everything will be ruined.
Leave it to me.
I have a plan.
Waiting for whom?
You bad guy.
I thought I had been deserted.
Why didn't reply me?
Why refused to see me?
If I hadn't threatened you with annunciator,
you'd still be avoiding me, right?
Come here.
I'm sorry.
Everything happened suddenly.
I still need some time.
So
what's the result of you consideration?
Respect our relationship.
What do you mean?
Cherish our time together.
Even if it's only one day left, I'll still cherish the day.
Even if it's only one second left,
I'll still cherish the second.
After all, in the rest of my life,
I won't open my chest
for another woman.
Still hurts?
No.
What about you?
What's your thought?
I...
won't leave.
Won't leave?
I mustn't return if I leave.
The outer space is in chaos recently.
It's hard to support the next space travel.
And my age is due.
The system will assign me a partner.
The law will force us to marry.
But you'll die if you stay.
Just die then.
Do you know?
I knew a kind of life on your earth,
It called mayfly.
They're born in every morning
and die before the sun sets.
Every part of their body
is totally designed for love.
Their mouth has degenerated
and full of bubbles in their stomach.
But,
to be suitable to fly lightly,
hungry as they are,
they only eat fluid food.
They have only one day to live.
During the day,
they have only one mission,
find a partner
to complete the mating.
After that,
they will die peacefully.
They are born for love
and end up with love.
Can I be your mayfly?
We'll always be together.
Ok?
Thanks for your understanding.
Thanks for letting us meet.
But now,
I don't need you anymore.
What are you doing?
I heard it from Xiaobu
that pressing will activate the annunciator.
Come on.
You lie to me!
I'd rather let you hate me
than see you die, Xiaoqi.
You despicable!
I am.
Cause I'm human.
Lying, being selfish.
These are all the nature of human.
To reach goals,
we can be regardless of anything.
I'm sorry.
But,
isn't love also the nature?
Do you really love me?
Is it that you loved me
because of the annunciator?
Now the annunciator has been taken out,
so you don't need me anymore.
Love has another name.
It's "do you a favor". Xiaoqi.
Do you remember
the first time I met you?
You said you were like a fairy
descending from the heaven.
In my heart,
you're always outgoing and reckless,
not fragile and feeble like now.
So I want you to go back to your planet.
You'll be
reborn there.
There's still some time before the spaceship arrives.
Before that,
can you
promise me one thing?
Say.
Look at me.
I want to reestablish the memory bank.
Let's
fall in love again.