Timing and Subtitles Brought To You by Lean on Me Team @ Viki.com
♫ Happiness is nagging next to my ears ♫
♫ My youth is smiling and showing its dimples ♫
♫ Love is raindrops in the form of candy ♫
♫ Raining down one by one ♫
♫ The sunshine is swirling around in my eyes ♫
♫ Warming up snippets of my memories ♫
♫ There are so much that I can't bear to say ♫
♫ They're held in my heart, radiating warmth ♫
♫ Continuously reenacting the light breeze, the stars
and the moon ♫
♫ covering the whole sky ♫
♫ Our little times and long years ♫
♫ Let’s talk about it slowly, no need to be in a rush ♫
♫ The sky in the distance is so comfortably warm ♫
♫ Just like the sunny and cloudless day when we first met ♫
♫ Our little times are brimming with fragrance ♫
♫ Growing up comfortably in the ruckus ♫
♫ Recalling our happiness, all has been well since we
last parted ♫
♫ It deserves to be kept forever, never forgotten ♫
[Put Your Head On My Shoulder]
I'll let you know what the difference between your brother and me is.
[Episode 20]
Gu Weiyi.
Gu Weiyi, did you bring a cone shell out with you?
I'm going to be late! I–!
- What are you doing?
- Going to work. I'm going to be late!
I took a day off for you.
- Really?
- Really.
Then I'm going to go back to sleep.
What's that on your neck?
Alcohol rash? I'm a bit allergic to alcohol.
If you knew you were allergic, why did you still drink so much?
I didn't do it on purpose.
You drank until you got to that state when I wasn't there. What were you thinking?
It was a work requirement.
I swear! I won't drink anymore. No matter what.
Even if I'm going to be fired.
Your face is like a scantron form and you reek of alcohol.
Am I?
You can't go to that kind of occasion in the future.
And don't contact that male celebrity as often anymore, got it?
Hurry and take a shower. I'm going to buy breakfast.
I want the fried dough sticks from the first breakfast store,
bean milk from the third store. I want peanut milk, not soybean milk.
- Go take a shower.
- Yes, Sir!
- You're back?
- Yeah.
Did you buy the peanut milk?
I bought it.
Come and eat breakfast.
Wait a moment.
What are you washing? Go eat breakfast, I'll help you–
What are you doing?
This... This i-is... my...
I know!  It fell to the ground. I rinsed it for you before hanging it up again.
N-No need.
It's fine. Didn't you wash it before you hung it up? It's not like it wasn't washed.
I know. Go eat breakfast.
Do you want one?
No.
- Do you want a sip?
- No.
I have a younger brother in my family. I hang up all of our laundry.
I'm used to it.
That's why there's no need to be shy.
I have no evil thoughts.
We've slept together in the same bed and nothing happened.
There's indeed no difference with my younger brother.
Gu Weiyi! Gu Weiyi! Gu Weiyi! What are you doing, Gu Weiyi?!
Gu Weiyi! What are you doing?
I'll let you know what the difference between your brother and me is.
Gu Weiyi.
Master! Master! Mistress is calling for you.
Yuan Yuan, stop.
Command received.
Yuan Yuan... Why does Yuan Yuan know how to speak?
I-I remodeled it.
Gu Weiyi... Gu Weiyi, what are you doing?!
I have low blood sugar.
Isn't your body too weak?
You couldn't even stand up from having low blood sugar.
Your body is so weak and you still don't like exercising.
You're really not that different from my younger brother.
I didn't say anything. I didn't say anything.
I'm warning you. Don't say that I'm not any different from your younger brother.
There is a difference. There is definitely a difference.
What's the difference?
You... You...
You know how to remodel the vacuum robot. My brother doesn't.
What?
I wanted to ask you what you wanted to eat.
Let's go out and talk.
How about you wait in your room? I'll call you when it's done.
I'll watch you cook.
The water needs some time to boil, how about–?
I'll wait here.
Okay, wait here then. Call me when the water boils.
[4. Experiment procedures and important notices]
[What do I do when my girlfriend hides from me?]
- What are you doing?
- Reading a thesis.
Didn't I tell you to watch the water in the kitchen? Why are you in your room?
It's not boiling yet. I'm watching it.
How are you watching it in your room?
You'll know if you come over here.
Forget it. I'll look at it in the kitchen.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Look.
Here.
The water is boiling.
Okay.
Let's eat!
- Wait.
- What?
It's too hot.
Instant noodles should be eaten when it's hot– What are you doing?!
I want to get the remote controller.
There's an egg, too.
Are you not going to school today?
I'm preparing my graduation thesis.
When is my major's oral defense?
- You're asking me?
- Can't I talk to myself?
I'm doubtful about whether you can graduate or not.
I have a well-thought out plan.
She's out! She's out.
How was it?
What kind of questions did the teacher ask you?
The teacher said, "Since you've changed your career, I won't make it hard for you."
He let me out after asking me a few questions.
Will I make it in time if I change my career now?
- There's no time.
- Wang Shan!
Here! Mo Mo, let's go eat later.
Okay.
I'm going to watch Gu Weiyi's oral defense. Physics' oral defense is open to the public.
- Tell Gu Weiyi to treat us to a meal then.
- We're broke!
- You have to treat us even if you have no money!
- No!
You have to!
How would you use an experiment to prove a relationship between viscosity and molecular weight?
Please explain.
♫ Happiness is nagging next to my ears ♫
[Southern University Physics 2018 Graduation Thesis Oral Defense]
♫ My youth is smiling and showing its dimples ♫
♫ Love is raindrops in the form of candy ♫
♫ Raining down one by one ♫
♫ The sunshine is swirling around in my eyes ♫
♫ Warming up snippets of my memories ♫
♫ There are so much that I can't bear to say ♫
♫ They're held in my heart, radiating warmth ♫
♫ Our little times and long years ♫
♫ Let’s talk about it slowly, no need to be in a rush ♫
♫ The sky in the distance is so comfortably warm ♫
♫ Just like the sunny and cloudless day when we first met ♫
♫ Our little times are brimming with fragrance ♫
♫ Growing up comfortably in the ruckus ♫
♫ Recalling our happiness, all has been well since we
last parted ♫
♫ It deserves to be kept forever, never forgotten ♫
Then, tell us why you wanted to choose
a research topic about partial polymer?
It's because the last time during class,
the teacher broke the Ubbelohde viscometer.
I used that opportunity to make some remodeling changes to it.
Gu Weiyi, are there any areas that are lacking in your thesis?
Was my question too superficial?
The topic of his thesis was already quite unpopular.
I think it's better if you don't ask that.
How about this?
About Student Gu's thesis, do the students and teachers present
have any other questions? You can ask as much as you want.
I–
Student Gu's oral defense will end here.
Okay. Thank you, Teachers.
Who are you calling?
- Was it fun?
- It was quite fun.
Let's go. Let's go eat.
Shan Shan and the group wanted you to treat us to a meal.
Can I just give the money and not go?
- What do you think?
- I say yes.
I say that you can't. Let's go.
- Are there more?
- Yes.
- There's more?
- Please wait a moment.
Did you order too much? This restaurant is quite expensive. Do you have enough money?
I do. I've already calculated it.
What have you calculated?
- Mo Mo!
- Mo Mo.
Wow!
Why do I think Gu Weiyi is richer
than your Fu Pei, the rich second generation?
Sit down! Sit down! Don't talk while standing. Sit.
Mo Mo, you understand me.
Gu Weiyi, what you've ordered here
are all my favorites.
You ordered so much, we can't finish them.
Youthful one, don't easily say "no" when you're faced with good food.
Also, we can pack it for takeaway if we can't finish it.
Niu Niu, what happened to your diet plan?
Don't you know that when dieting, you need to eat as much as you can in moderation
to cheat your body, that you're still the same fatty
so that your body will give you the same rate of metabolism?
Otherwise, the rate of metabolism is going to go down.
All right!  All right! Stop talking, let's start eating. Move those chopsticks!
Eat more.
Come find me after you're finished.
[Okay]
Don't be shocked. Eat.
- You've never been to this place, right?
- No.
This place isn't bad.
Quite comfortable.
Brat, stop playing with your phone.
This is your classmate from your school, Lu Jianshi.
Student Lu is a pillar of the country. She's a talent that's returned from abroad.
She specialized in studying quantum force.
It's quantum mechanics.
Let's order dishes first. Let's order.
Waitress.
What's the most expensive dish you have here?
- I have an important guest with me today.
- Fish.
How expensive could fish be?
Do you know how to recommend dishes? Tell your manager to come here.
Mister, our fish is all flown in by air from Canada.
I don't care where it was flown in from.
I just want the most expensive dish.
¥3,800 (US$543) for each tael (50 grams).
I guess it doesn't have to be that expensive.
Thank you. Give us one catty (500 grams) of that fish.
Jianshi, do you think that we should order that fish?
I'm fine with anything.
Then I think there is every need to eat this fish today.
That's how it can show my dad's love to you.
Right, Dad?
Give us one catty then.
- Bill, please.
- Just a moment.
A total of ¥3,453.
(approx. $495.70)
How much?
¥3,453.
What did we eat that's that expensive? Are you tricking us?
Miss, do you want to check the receipt?
- There's no need.
- Why is there no need? There must be a problem.
The red wine was ¥899, marbled beef was ¥298,
- Yangtze Grenadier Anchovy was ¥1,100.
- This...this...
What fish was ¥1,100?
Yangtze Grenadier Anchovy.
Do you mean the dish filled with pineapple mixed with four to five pieces of sweet and sour fish?
¥7,800 for one catty.
Gu Weiyi, are you insane? ¥7,800 for one catty of fish?
Miss, ¥7,800 for one carry of fish is not that expensive.
The restaurant next door has fish flown in by air from Canada selling for ¥3,800 for one tael.
I was worried that you'd think I was being stingy with your friends.
Also, I didn't buy the one that's ¥3,800 for one tael.
If you paid ¥3,800 for one tael, I'd go home and dismantle Yuan Yuan!
Mister. Miss. Are you able to pay the bill now?
Should I get a receipt for you then?
No. Do you have enough money? I have some.
I do. I calculated it perfectly.
- Can I use WeChat?
- Yes.
"Your card with numbers ending in 071 paid ¥3,453 on June 8th at 8:00.
"Remaining amount ¥0.12."
You really did calculate it perfectly.
We've only been eating the fish.
I didn't even properly introduce my son to you.
He is studying management at the same school as you.
He has quite good grades. He plays basketball well, too.
But I already have a girlfriend.
She is prettier than Miss Lu, too.
She seems to be much prettier.
Hello, Uncle. Hello.
I'll ceremoniously introduce her to you two. This is my girlfriend, Wang Shan.
What nonsense are you speaking? I don't agree with it!
Why do you care?
Did China's education system not teach you that there should be respect in people's interactions?
Mutual respect? Miss Lu, I didn't hear it wrong, did I?
When you were eating fish that cost tens of thousands, were you thinking of respect?
Seems like the "respect" that they teach overseas isn't worth much either.
Today's meal wasn't bad. Luxurious.
I'm satisfied.
I'll be leaving first with my girlfriend then.
Stop right there! If you dare step out that door, just you try!
You're rebelling, you!
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
Look at you! Look at you! You don't even act like a man!
How did I get such a good-for-nothing son like you?!
Uncle, you're not in a good mood today,
so I won't introduce myself in detail today.
I'll come and visit you with Fu Pei next time.
Fu Pei, let's leave.
Fu Pei! Fu Pei!
What is it?
N-Nothing. I just found it funny.
Didn't you see my dad's expression? He nearly died from anger.
Did I go overboard just now?
But your dad's attitude to you...
No, it was really good.
Let's go.
I'm so hungry.
- Here.
- I don't want to drink water anymore.
I can't drink anymore.
I think that we're going to die if we continue like this.
Then let's eat a pack of instant noodles.
You dare to?
We finished up a month's spending on a meal. That's our last pack of instant noodles.
My scholarship will be sent before we graduate.
Can't we use my money?
No.
Are we going to drink and eat wind before you get the scholarship money?
There will be a solution.
But if we don't eat that pack of instant noodles now,
we won't make it to our graduation photos.
Fine.
It smells so good.
Not only does it smell good, but there's also a surprise, too.
Where did it come from?
When I was looking for a pack of instant noodles in the fridge, I found it stuck in the gap inside the fridge.
So, I put it in as well.
You eat it.
You should eat it.
There's only one, so you can have it.
You eat it. I'm not hungry.
Here–
Don't waste it. Don't waste it.
Eat the noodles.
Eat more vegetables.
Eat more, eat more of this.
It tastes so good.
Is it delicious?
Where did the egg go?
Where did it go? Where is it?
Eat the noodles. Eat more.
Drink more of the soup; it'll fill your stomach.
It's so delicious.
Do you know how to tie a tie?
I-I was about to ask you.
I remember the way they tied it in the video is similar to tying a red scarf.
It should go around here and...
Isn't it like that?
Around like this and then around like this...go around like this.
Just tie it however. We're going to be late.
Don't rush me, I can tie it.
It's starting to look like the shape of a tie.
Okay, okay, okay!
- Okay! Job done!
- I'll tie it for you.
I'll ask Lu Lu to tie it for me at school. Let's go!
[Sending off the graduates of 2018, come back home to visit often.]
[From a student card to an alumni card, continue to study a lot even after you graduate.]
[Auntie's hand wasn't shaking, she wants you to be thin, you're cooking for yourself from now on, eat less.]
[Waving goodbye, open your sails and sail far.]
[Put what you've learned to good use, connect the hearts of the world]
Stay up late less, your health is important.
[Lights won't be turned off by force anymore, but you still should sleep early]
Hey, Lu Lu.
Are you excited to see Ah Ke in a graduation gown?
Ah Ke already took a photo and showed me. What I'm most expectant of now
is what Gu Weiyi and Fu Pei look like in a graduation gown.
The two of them have such small faces and long legs,
they will surely be handsome.
You can only look at Mo Mo's man, don't look at my man.
- I'm going to look. I want to look at both.
- I want to see, too.
Shan Shan!
- Fu Pei!
- Shan Shan!
Is this the school grass (most handsome guy) from our school?
It feels like his IQ is really low.
- Who has low IQ?
- It's you.
I have something to give to you.
Ta-da! Were you surprised?
Was it prickly when you put it inside?
- It was. But I held it in.
- Prick you, prick you.
- Exactly.
- Was it prickly?
- As long as you're happy.
Lu Lu! Lu Lu! Tie my tie for me!
- Hold this for me for a moment.
- They smell nice.
- You know how to tie it, right?
- I do!
Why do you guys have graduation gowns?
We got it for you.
- I'll change into it in the dorms then.
- Where are you? Come to the lab quickly for photos.
Okay. I'll go there now.
- Do you know how to tie it?
- I do!
- I'm going to the lab first.
- I'll come here to meet up later.
- Okay.
Wait. I have a graduation photo plan.
That way, we won't miss every scene that we have memories of.
I realize that you're doing things with plans more and more now.
- Of course. Why don't you look at who's teaching me so well?
- Let me see.
[Everyone is waiting for you, hurry up.]
I made an electronic version too. I'll send them to your phones later.
- Zhou Lei keeps rushing me. I'm leaving first.
- Go ahead.
- See you later.
- Bye-bye.
Why did your boyfriend leave right after coming? Does he have a woman hidden at the lab?
- Don't say anymore. They do have a really pretty senior at the lab.
- Lu Lu!
What kind of pretty girls could there be at the lab?
I swear!  The gods are watching. I was just curious.
Also, I heard that she really likes Gu Weiyi.
It's not like what you're thinking.
Mo Mo, you're so understanding now.
Look at Gu Weiyi, he didn't even give you a flower.
Exactly. Look at Fu Pei.
For Wang Shan, he got his chest pricked.
He didn't remember. You guys don't have flowers either, right?
- I do. I have flowers in my heart.
- In my heart.
In your heart... All right! Go, go, go! Let's go take photos!
- Shan Shan, sit tight.
- Let's go take photos!
Let's go.
Why are you so heavy?
[To be continued, there are easter eggs...]
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You by Lean on Me Team @ Viki.com
I'm so full.
We're going to take graduation photos soon.
If you continue eating like this, I'm not going to photoshop for you.
I'll ask Mo Mo to help me then.
We've made you spend a lot today. Sorry.
The meal we meant was a barbecue.
We didn't think you were going to be so honest. Since you were being so honest,
we'll be honest with you, too.
Save me, Shan Shan! Let go of your hands!
- Situ Mo's ears are really sensitive.
- Save me!
This meal was well-spent, right?!
- What did she say?
- She didn't say anything.
I'm leaving first. Thanks for the meal.
- Take care!
- Got it.
- What did they say to you?
- Nothing.
Nothing? What did they really say to you?
I told you, it was nothing.
I don't believe it.
- Stop asking.
- Then, why are you blushing?
From the perspective of biology, the secretion of adrenaline will cause blood to flow to the capillaries in the surface of the skin.
- The expansion of the capillaries at the surface of the skin will–
- Enough. Don't say anything anymore.
♫ Love the corner of your lips, love your eyelashes ♫
♫ Love the tips of your hair, love your taste ♫
♫ The signal in your eyes, the little pride in your pout ♫
♫ They are all your exclusive expression packs ♫
♫ Love your intonation, love your coquettishness ♫
♫ Love your smile, oh, love your hug ♫
♫ You playing up to me like a kitty, my defence is all useless ♫
♫ No one can replace this kind of feeling ♫
♫ Holding your hand, step by step by step by step,
circling around you ♫
♫ Feeling this love, bit by bit by bit, becoming clearer ♫
♫ Grateful to have met you, I’m even smiling in my sleep ♫
♫ Just like this, it makes my heart skip a beat ♫
♫ Letting sweetness, day by day by day by day, slowly
fermenting ♫
♫ Baking the taste of romance ♫
♫ This level of sweetness is just right, I want to eat it
in one bite ♫
♫ One serving of the bread of love tastes like two
servings of happiness ♫
♫ Holding your hand, step by step by step by step,
circling around you ♫
♫ Feeling this love, bit by bit by bit, becoming clearer ♫
♫ Grateful to have met you, I’m even smiling in my sleep ♫
♫ Just like this, it makes my heart skip a beat ♫
♫ Letting sweetness, day by day by day by day, slowly
fermenting ♫
♫ Baking the taste of romance ♫
♫ This level of sweetness is just right, I want to eat it
in one bite ♫
♫ One serving of the bread of love tastes like two
servings of happiness ♫